from the shadows of the sub conscious to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls this is psyche
awakens crowd whoosh sparkly chimes thundercrack you smooth mystical yo welcome to the madness
buckle in tight tear it on deck third eye in flight truce get told he goes unfold we
Trolls be dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
It's like the Awake has stepped in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so big play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
It's like the Awake has don't look away
Your shadow's talkin', it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
Can you guys hear me okay?
Hi.
Oh, it's morning time.
Oh, you're up pretty early.
Hi, good morning.
How do I look?
Breasted.
I had like Jack in the box in the middle of the night.
I'm sitting here in my underwear.
No, yeah, kinda.
Hello
I don't know I try to you know
Let's see DJ Electra introduced me to
Creating AI songs and videos and I don't think there's anything I don't have any I
Did take piano lessons for a few years, but I'm not good at
piano
even writing lyrics, so but I
Know it would make a funny song usually and so I
Don't know AI is the talent people don't understand you have to like know what to
Prompt it to do. It's like knowing how to ask the right questions kind of thing. Which is the talent
Not like you know
playing it all my all the instruments and you know vocal it would just take a whole
You know $20,000 in a big bag and you can use them learn things. I don't think there's anything wrong with it
But to be criticized like I'm like, you know, I'm like just like some kind of I
Don't know it's pretty very evil twist on
Just trying to like be people laugh. I don't know
Sometimes I want to tell people they're going kind of going off the deep end like with their like criticism. I don't know
I'm talking about
It's like
It's the dealio this won't even like shit
Mmm, I hate these cigars all the cigars they have the backwards
Hi guys, oh shit. It's terrible
Hi anyhow, I'm I'm very early this morning
That I mean have you really seen me criticize anybody like
Have a show start a show. I just like go after a specific person
No
That wouldn't do that
But you guys know I sure am getting some shit
She was Satan's ex, with that fiery stare.
Told me my rising sign, like she actually
Without you, I'm stuck in hell
Hmmm.
Hahaha.
She dumped me.
In a really mean way.
Very mean.
What I mean is beta.
Beta is just evil.
Emma.
It was misunderstanding.
Hmmm.
Why?
Next is gonna be the Lisa Jordanna song, but that's a happier song
Number beat of songs I'm not wasting any more time on that
That is just some black hole that I don't want to go back into
With the link okay morning everybody I'm like here my boxers is working. Oh
Please
Fish lips. No, I think she has fish. I mean she has like these pours us
Kiss me gorgeous lift
II
Okay. Hi guys
Huh, I'm gonna but I'm gonna introduce it on her show, you know, it'll be fun like
Hello
Hi
Experience style link. Oh fair link. Where for out thou link?
You know what? What play what play? You know what play?
We're for at the link with it. Let's do the Hamlet version
Juliet Juliet Juliet Juliet cuz I just you know all the shit
Yeah
What part that Romeo?
I was in Romeo and Juliet.
I was, too.
I played Paris.
Who'd you play?
It was somebody like, let me see.
It wasn't Mercutio, but it was like, I don't know,
somebody was talking to him.
Tibble or something?
I don't remember exactly.
Somebody that was talking to Mercutio.
I like that.
You were probably in a lot of plays, though, right?
I was I wasn't actually I can just come community theater. I was in I was in bye-bye birdie
I was in sugar. I played a gangster and sugar like Chicago gangster
But you know it was that it was a Marilyn Monroe movie. I don't know if you saw it
It's had Jack. I think Jack lemon Marilyn Monroe. What's the name of it?
It's called some like it hot, but it was certain to
That's famous I've seen it before I gotta watch that again though. I gotta watch that yeah
Because I'll tell you something
Because hanging out on your panel so much and watching your reruns. I've not watched as a lot of movies as I used to
I'm serious like I've definitely yeah like I usually watch
so you know how best picture there's like ten nominees now they used to be five
yeah and best actor there's five nominees backed act so i used to watch every single movie that
was nominated for the five major academy awards like always you know and i've been really slack in
the past two years since i've been on the youtube streets especially since i started watching you
Well, good. I'm glad I'm like you see my rear because I put all the reruns on like members only and like because
You know, there's people that want to try to flag my episodes and stuff like that
So I just put it for the members and stuff like that. That's smart. That's smart
But then it's like, you know, good times is the same yesterday on beaters. Oh, you charge is people to come on the panel
But it's totally misrepresenting. It's wrong
The noise mr. Resenting and then it's like don't even talk about it right now you're talking about it
He's smiling forget it. Seriously. You're good. Everybody knows you're good
I mean, of course if you want to talk about it, you can but I'm just trying to help you like yeah
Don't even talk about it. Don't even bring it. Don't even bring it up
Well, I mean, I mean, yeah, I won't even bring up him, but it's like, and then, and then, like, yesterday, like, Bita was just like, it was just pure attack, like, and I just, like, on purpose, I was like, either silent or just, like, gracious, and just to see, it's like, I might have, but I continued being attacked just for, like, doing nothing.
You know what you should do? You should know what you should do? You should charge people to come up on the panel, like, like, I just came up here, you should say, like, school, you got to drop a dollar if you want to come up on the panel. What do you think of that?
Well, I think it's good. I mean like yesterday in this week. I've been like doing you know
I if someone donated today, I'll just say okay. I'll do like I'll do I'll do a panel
You know like I'll do yeah, this one's on donated
Yeah, you taught me about that how much is it close to sponsor
$10 for like three hours, and then it's like plus you get your ad for the three hours
Like whatever like you know if you have a website or whatever you want to promote if you want to save message on the banner
You can be there for three hours. I mean, it's like it's pretty good deal actually. I'll do that. I'll do that
I get to write whatever I want on the banner sure
Anything I want anything if you want to mess it. I mean, it's not against the TOS
I'm happy with anything you want to put on I don't mean like that. I shouldn't have like anything I want
I'm just yeah, I mean, I'm not gonna fucking like it's not gonna be hate speech or anything like that
Yeah, no, no, I mean, I know you'd be responsible that that's just like you know, and I have like this
There's the banner right there that says you can sponsor the panel and then it's like
But I'll put whatever you want on the banner if you can you can type it out and I'll put it there
Who's the best-looking actor you think under 55 guy wise? Who do you think?
That's kind of hard because you know, it's like Johnny Depp and Tom Cruise and the
60s now yeah
Leo DeCaprio Ryan Gosling, you know, I like Joaquin Phoenix a little bit, you know, like, you know, River Phoenix's brother
All right. All right. All right. He was a joker. I mean, it's like he's
This is it Joaquin. So this is a simile what I'm about to do. This is an SAT question
All right Joaquin Phoenix. No wait, here we go ready
No, cuz he's newer actually. Well, who's your favorite? Um, like older like Jack Lennon. Who's it like?
I like like rock Hudson, you know, I like a carry Grant, you know, he's
Yeah, yeah, carry grants carry grants one. He's the top ten all time for me
carry Grant is to Marilyn Monroe as
blank is to
Um, what's that girl's name? That's in transform is that was married to Brian Austin green
Vanessa Marcell you thinking of
Megan yeah, thank you, hon. Who's that? This is respectfully
respectfully
Apologetic
Just don't get it. Yeah, can you run to the
Don't forget it and you don't
It's a good song. Yeah, so hey, my mom
Thank you. Hey everybody. Yeah, we are very good morning. I just like you know
I'm syndicated on
On rumble, you know, there's somebody named I think clip clip talk or trip kick or maybe somebody else
They syndicate a bunch of the panel burst
They have a channel on rumble called panel burst and so you can like watch reruns of my show beat his show
The good times on there Q45
You know
Instead and watch it on psyche's channel become a member and you can watch reruns on psyche's channel
Definitely, it's a lot easier to watch them here than on rumble plus it's like you're supporting
But but I do get to like watch you know reruns of betas and things that you know
You people don't necessarily get to see because you know leads all our episodes, right? So
Yeah, Beatis Kitties, she's had the channel, Beatis Kitties BKG.
I mean, Beatay was one of the first streamers, and she really did support my channel.
I thought I was hoping to support her channel, but we were fighting every other day.
Why are you fighting?
I have no idea
She's the she goes through through different moves and so she's this move. She's mad at me
But no, maybe we'll be friends again tomorrow. I mean, I think it's just gets very dizzy
But uh, anyway, I don't know. I don't know if you saw any first show yesterday. It was the
I'm a mod in her chat. So it's kind of funny. It's like a I think she has a love hate thing for me
and this is all the hate right now, but
You know, you know, don't fight in front of the children. I don't know. I'm going to I'm gonna
I'm gonna make a big deal out of it and like, you know, you bother but I should I shouldn't I know
I'm gonna shut up. I'm gonna shut up, but
So how is you how are you guys this morning? I have a little bit of heartburn and digestion from the jack-of-box
They in the middle of the night, so
You know that we do do an intervention. I mean we do and I like oh I'll go over to our chat one time and just like
sit her out and say
you know, you're gonna go to rehab center in Malibu or
Or nothing, I don't know. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. No, I should be going to rehab. Actually, I've been drinking so much
So, but you notice I haven't been drinking too much lately. I thought I had two drinks
You know, I'm a so I'm a and I
Taking day-to-day's off this week of drinking too. And so, you know, I'm actually also clean my apartment
Like is pretty clean in here right now. It's not perfect, but it's like, you know, I have like
Yeah
Okay
It's not dangerous like there's nice places of nice parts of it. I'm gonna nice for part of LA, but there are
You know, I don't I don't think you have any problem like nobody
Think there's a lot of people with tattoos available at Berkeley my mom my mom had tattoos though
Wait, what's the question here? I have specific tattoos and they're okay being gang-affiliated whatsoever whatsoever
Wait, that was my question actually are any of your tattoos gang-affiliated you just answered that you said no
No, um, but so some people they might look that way depending on yeah. Yeah
Right
Where and stuff
You're not gonna have a problem with having stars. I have
No
like they have them on their neck and stuff but uh anyway do you know the biggest gang do you
know what the biggest gang in america is trivia question blood bloods and crypts no no the police
the police oh the police okay yeah
that's right yeah there's the LAPD has the bandidos and they're like actually they have tattoos
they have their own tattoos and they're actually a gang right you ever see a police officer that
has the blue line flag on his on his arm that's disgraceful that blue line flag they they have
a tattoo of a blue lined american flag that's blacked out on their arm and they
you know they swore an oath to the american flag and they put the blue line flag that's all i
want to say to that i mean long as they got that badge they're bitching to have that's right that's
you're right well i mean if you said if you had the people that took oaths that were above the
oath of as an american citizen you'd probably be very surprised and it's like right to just be a
righteous person i couldn't hear you it's like like someone table-taking oaths outside of like
Yeah, like people have like like more respect to like you know certain organizations that they're in than their own country
You know and so
We'll fall in place depending on you know the situation respect is always first respect yourself and respect others
Yeah, well, I agree, but also like respect the country and like, you know, I think it's a country is our country first
You know or actually as the even as a world citizen a human being first
you know and
People put all kinds of other things first, you know, I mean even like you're you know, you put your family first. That's fine
You might have to suck tuck your tail. So, you know, you're back as it gets the long as shit
And I know I know she does sound young younger, but she is 31 we verified. I mean, she's verified
Okay
I'm taking courses, but no
for the people, for the person that's asking in the comments or whatever.
Yeah, we got some wild people in this chat.
But as everyone's doing today, they aren't using the youngsters slang, yeah.
Yeah, well, I haven't dealt with really police for like, uh, I
Since I moved back to redondo, I've been pulled over here twice and that's just I don't have a car so pulled over walking
You know, I pulled over walking and then uh, you know, but I've been in no trouble
since I moved here eight years ago and
Actually, my uncle was the sergeant of the police department here
And so that's what I always, you know, let them know if I ever do get pulled over
He was a sergeant in the 80s and early 90s
Katrina um are you talking about you said she hasn't said brah even once um brah you say brah
no i don't uh i think she's that person says katrina's talking about me but um no i'm that's kind
How everyone's
Like Logan Paul, I mean it's like who speaks like that really but Logan Paul and oh
Yeah, I think it's we lost Athens, but
But I don't even be listening to this show or like and what do you like about this show?
RC did you go to Howard?
I don't even is that like a
Are you African-american who me? Uh-huh. Um, yeah, actually
Okay. Yeah, Howard. I think Howard, you know, am I wrong that Howard mixed? Okay. Howard University
I think is like kind of like is am I wrong guys? Is that am I thinking of Brown University or something?
But there's like a kind of a famous black university. I think Howard is one of them.
Maybe. Yeah, because yeah, there's some schools they have like the Boulay. Have you heard the Boulay?
There's a society called the Boulay. It's like a secret society kind of paternal organization. That's a I guess like
Is it on Howard University? It's been some black universities. I know and then it's like a lot of people with the White House
She under 20 no, I'm not whatever I I'm not gonna be combative
Believe what you want to believe but I'll be 31 in August. Yes. Yeah, she's 30. I'm 44
Vicky so so Vicky and I are friends, you know Vicky actually came over to my tiktok and was in my chat on tiktok
I think I don't know if I made her mom. No, I made really Nancy moderate
I need to make Vicky a moderator so because she's like this lady CV and it's like it's and she's a she's super cool and nice
Yes, I did see her boobs. I think she showed me her boobs back say
I don't know if it was a joke or she like has a crush on me or something
But she's a nice lady and I like her. I like her. What's up?
No, I was reading his comments. Oh, okay. Yeah
Yeah, I don't know. It was she has many small nipples, but she had very large
Whatever they I mean, it's like they were just it was there they're big
I mean as she was like laughing and she was like and then she was like it was like almost like she had him like up past her ears
I mean it was like it was just like a very strange sight, but
Yeah, I think she's cool because she's supported me on tiktok and so
Um, and then she's like, you know messaging me there and stuff. I think she wants to be a mod here
So I used to hear I forgot her name though. I think she said her name was Vicky on here. So
I'll go ahead and mark. Yeah, right. It was is that is that you are you mama Maria?
I mean, I don't want to like rate them because it's like I want to be night
I want to be just nice and say
Everyone is everyone is all different shapes and sizes and everyone's beautiful in their own way. I'll so I'll stay
Sorry, sorry go ahead. No, I was just reading the comments. Okay. Yeah, I
Don't know is that CV I don't know is that CV to I can
No, it's like I do like I do have fun on tiktok though and
Did you ever go on tiktok?
Respectfully
Am I on tiktok? No
I'm not into all the like
Number one, I'm very impatient. I'm trying to learn how to gain patience and shit like that
considering I got a maneuver within this world with other people and shit. So therefore, like, I don't...
It's not purposely, but I don't text.
I don't um, I don't download all these apps and shit like that or whatever and get savvy with all these apps
It's just too much for me. Yeah, I shut down
It's like, you know, like I started my YouTube channel like knowing like, you know that YouTube channels can get monetized
But it's very difficult to monetize
Actually, I was able to get monetized in like a few months and then actually
Monetize means I can offer memberships and so I can put content behind the paywall and offer special things for members like
Just like all the content is just for free for members only I get to a lot of memberships
I can also get super chats and also I'm you know ad revenue
But I really don't put many ads on my any of my videos. I basically just do the memberships and super chats
Also, I have cash apps set up too.
I have different ways of monetizing just means making money.
I really wanted to be able to make money from home on my own.
I've been trying for years and years and years.
I was always like, yeah.
Are you still on TikTok?
Yeah.
So I just started my TikTok, and...
No, no, no they it was like for maybe for one day or something there was like some kind of thread of it
Cuz it is owned by China I think but I think it's gonna stay open, but it does allow you to
To maybe or they should be maybe like an alternative to it. I don't know American can make one
Yeah, but um, you know, you basically scroll through these videos. I'm monetized there
I can make I can have them you know the membership there within three days
And so it's like if you just want to put yourself out there like and then you know
I have people like to just find you and you if you especially if you have a business to promote to
Take talk is really good because I can promote my terror readings
I can promote a YouTube channel there like basically without doing anything automatically
It just has an autoresponder that will send emails to people and like and I'm get I get just people writing back to me
Like just from the autoresponder. So it's pretty cool. It's really good for business
So I don't know what's going on in chat like someone they're talking about nipples and stuff like that
But and then a bulbous sack. I don't know. Yeah, people people do uh, thank you last week backstage
Okay, okay
Yeah, people flash me backstage sometimes and sometimes it's good, but it's like usually it's not very good
It's like
Like maybe like one or two times it's been okay, but then it's like usually it's like disgusting
Yeah, I saw all these balls the other day and that was like really like he looks so nice from like the way
So he looked like he looked was like really like nicely put together like otherwise
He looked like a nice nice man, and then all of a sudden like he says terrible things and then he shows his balls
And I just had that was like, you know
terrible they don't look good they mean it's like it's just like it's just yeah
so Aldi did that yesterday I think or the day before yesterday
And so he's bad from the show and then people are like, oh, don't fan all the Emily
Well, he showed his balls three times you understand that can like hurt my monetization. It's like people don't understand
It's like I'm actually a monetized channel. I'm trying to keep my channel. I don't want all these, you know
Disgusting balls having an effect on my show. I know and it's like it was it's like no reason to and it's like I had him back on
So anyway
Oh gosh, okay, so I bought these like backwoods and they're so gross and it's like it's all I have to smoke today
It's like this back way and it's like not even tobacco. It's like all shredded like
These things all shredded like paper. Hey, thank you school that's in
Is that what you want to the banner at then so you know thank you for the super chat
Thank you for the fortnight super chat. Terry Grant is the Marilyn Monroe a psyche is to Megan Fox. Oh, okay
Wow
Yeah
That's a good one. I'll also leave the comment on the screen a little bit
And if you want me to pay Sebastian if you want me to program my banner with that I will do so
Um, let me see
So yeah, it's an early morning show because I've been so tired in the afternoons and nights
And then I like I've been I got some good sleep
Every all I dream about is like not nightmare in Elm Street, but like nightmare Elm Street type
Feeling to it. Like Freddy's not there, but it's like it's like the TV show Freddy's nightmares
You have to watch that on it's on YouTube. I think some of the episodes. Have you ever seen it Freddy's nightmares?
Yeah, they had like a snippet of it on on to be
On to be yeah, they might have yeah, they might have some episodes. I think they might have some episodes. It's from the 80s
Look last time I watched a scary movie was
like almost two months ago, I believe probably about two months, and I'm
like
What do you see? Huh? What did you see? I watched the none too
The nun to okay, that sounds horrifying
Was the nun evil was the nun is an evil person or what was the nun doing?
Why was the nun scary his nuns usually like this like scared to get like you like your hand with
Go to YouTube like the video thing and then type in nun to
Okay
Yeah, well, I guess nuns are scary, I mean, it's like they're, you know, if you go to
Catholic school, you're going to...
None.
It presents itself as a nun, but it's an entity.
Okay.
So it's a it looks like a nun. It's like that's it's like avatar or yeah, it takes the form of a nun
Just look okay, look you'll see it is scary is it scarier than like it or is it like?
No characters this particular thing the real character. Yeah, it is it's a spin-off from the conjuring
There's a country to the country three and the country four is getting ready to come out
so they introduced the
The demon I don't want to say the demon name, but the demon was introduced
to the world
As viewers on the conjuring too. Are you saying you believe in this demon in real life?
I don't want to I don't want to say
whether
Yeah, okay. Okay. I want to okay. I don't say too much don't say too much. Yeah, I don't want to I don't want to get this
pure it's all right
I just want you okay
Okay, I
Mean I'll look I'm gonna look it up. I'm gonna submit look up right now
Sight that you can go to well actually it's an app
They have free movies and shit and you can watch basically any fucking movie that just came out or whatever
So let me check it out the nun. Yeah, not the nun. Okay
The non-one is scary, but the non-two, it's, it's, whoa, it fucks with me.
It says, it says, in 1956 France, a priest is murdered and it seems an evil is spreading.
Sister Irene, once again, comes face to face with a demonic force.
Okay.
It's fucking scary, man.
It says...
In 1956, Father Noire and his alter-boy Jacques performed daily chores in their church in Tarasco in France.
While investigating a disturbance, Noire is raised into the air set on fire and burned to death before a terrified Jacques.
Four years after the events at St. Carthus Monastery, Sister Irene now serves in a convent in Italy.
Maurice works at a boarding school in France where he's befriended by a young Irish student named Sophie and her mother Kate.
who is a teacher at the school. Irene has a vision of Maureen's asking her to save him.
She's dispatched by the Cardinal to investigate a series of deaths across Europe.
Attributed to the demon, oh it is an actual Goetia demon, okay. It is spelled D-A-L-A-K,
but I won't say it, yeah. Yep, I tried to get it out my head and I hate that I even remember the
Well, I like to read about them actually
Fucks with me like seriously dude. It does. No, I'm not I don't have a problem that you're reading or anything. Absolutely not but like
That shit doesn't there's a picture. It's kind of like Cupid a little bit
Oh fuck shit and the movie
No, that's
That's not what was being presented in the movie at all both. How about you go to the trailer?
Well, I don't think I can play it. I'll watch it. I'll definitely watch it. But yeah, I
Can't play it on my show, but oh, I can watch it like on this I can watch on my tablet. Let me see that none, too
And so it's a scary like
Scary none. Let me see sweepy. I'm not I'm not mad. I'm not mad. It's me. I don't know why your wrenches
Is it on your old account or something?
Yeah, I'm taking out the trailer right now
Yeah, I'm watching that. Okay
so
Is it was in English or is this in Italian go to the nun to I'm watching it. See I'm watching it. Oh
Watching that via the trailer
See
Have you seen the classroom?
You know I haven't
Check this out, right?
Ed in Lorraine Ward
There. Oh, yeah, there they are
Investors like the Abigail the Abigail ball and stuff. Yeah, it seems to this right so the Abigail doll
that doll was
confined
sealed with um
The word of Jesus the holy Bible
It was okay, see the thing about it is like a few few years ago
I actually looked the shit up, right?
I was sitting in a hotel or whatever
and I looked the shit up
and I don't know why the fuck I did it.
But my mom always say, don't go searching for,
you know, I wasn't searching for it,
but it was more so like, I was curious.
I was curious about the documentaries of Ed
and Lorraine Warren before she, before she and he passed.
Because, right, when they put out the Conjuring one,
After that Ed and Lorraine Warren both passed away, okay, so when I first seen the Conjuring one I
Had just lost my son probably like a couple months prior, right?
So I went out to the movies and shit, you know with one of my friends or whatever and you know like I'm like
Okay, let's go to the movies and shit. I'm like I
Can't watch scary movies if I'm gonna be by myself
I like my solitude. I like to be solitary. It's it's what fits me
But if I watch a scary movie and I know I'm finna watch a scary movie
You gotta spend a night with me, you know saying like I cannot be by myself
I'll have the whole fucking house lit up like a fucking Christmas tree like Bill Hyatt's motherfucker
You know I'm saying so
Therefore I am I'm scary as fuck, but I love scary movies. That's what intrigues me. It's the the suspense or
Whatever the fuck but
The thing is like if you watch so much of that shit and the shit that you consume we are consumers
You know saying like I'm fucking TV
Fucking food like we are natural consumers. So like after a while or whatever I noticed that I
Don't want to cry
Because it fucking freaks me to fuck out.
It freaks me out.
Like my mom, my mom, she said.
She said really stop watching scary movies. Stop watching this shit
Stop watching it. My mom and my grandmother says it all the fucking time
You know, and I gave my mom my HBO account and I gave my mom my grandmother my HBO account
So my mom called me and she's like breathe. Why are you watching all these scary movies?
Stop, you know, and she she said that because it affects me
I am I am affected by
by things like
I'm very sensitive very very very fucking sensitive
Like my emotions mentally, you know, like this shit of the physical world don't fucking scare me
But the things that really scare me is a shit that I cannot see but I've seen some shit before
I've seen I've seen a fucking I've seen if I've seen something before I even took a picture of it like seriously
I'm not fucking bullshitting
Are you okay? Oh
I think we lost her. Oh
She put herself on mute. Okay. I'm gonna let her just take a breath and you know
She wants to continue the story, but you know feel free to come up and I wouldn't
you know, just take a take a second, you know to
catch your breath
No, it's not out to the God right there shout out to God he good shit God he okay
Like I said, I am affected by things that I'm very sensitive
I'm very in tune with my spirit. You know, I'm still learning myself. I'm yearning to learn but
It gets to a point where like, you know, I have to like drop to my knees and call on God call on Jesus
Yo, Gotti got to get up here, bro. She's calling for you
Right Gotti, she's dropping through her knees calling for you
I'm trying to make you laugh honey. Don't say it's like blow your nose girl. You know what I'm saying in a good in a good way
Okay, that's a joke. It's to laugh. You could we're trying to get you to laugh
It's like you tell her that I don't attack people. I'm up here to try to make us smile and laugh
Yeah, he's inside. He's very sensitive. I'm very sensitive. You heard me girl. You heard me girl. Yeah, I hear you or whatever
Thank you. Can I say one thing just respectfully because you know, we're all listening and everything and
I don't know if this
like
I am respectfully psyche
This is good for you right now right here. Like where where you're at. I think this platform
Might make you more upset respectfully and I don't mean psyche. So don't think that psyche's the greatest guy
Or are you assuming that I think that you're no, no, no, so so that's a great question
You see how you just asked me a question
See I was asking you that same question because like I said I think I didn't say I know
So now the next thing is is you talk to me about what I just said. Do you think that could be true?
Like I said, you're assuming that no, I just you see it's like easy. What's about to happen right now now
We're about to talk over each other and have an argument because she's not listening
Okay, right when you said are you assuming that I responded to you that it's a question and then I asked you to
Respond to it and how you feel and immediately you went negative and said I'm assuming that right after I said it's a question
And I'm not assuming it
Is it okay? Do you respond? Do you respond?
I don't want to argue with anybody. That's not what I'm here to do.
Wow. Yeah. Wow, psyche. I don't know what to say. I just, I just, you know, I will say this,
and this isn't about you respectfully. What was it again? Copacetic?
This isn't about you. This is in general like the way we interact today psyche. Would you agree with this statement that I'm making?
You often see people ask other people questions online like let's say on a YouTube forum somebody posts up a
A video right psyche and somebody asked that person a question on there
Hey, is it are you this are you that and immediately the person takes it as an accusation?
You know what I mean, and I find that
I'm not talking about you on you can respond if you want and interrupt, but go ahead
I appreciate you saying that and I'm gonna wrap this up with my plane in 15 seconds and I see that happening
Okay. Thank you. I think I heard that. I think you break it up a little bit, but thank you for that. Thank you for making that point.
But so you can go ahead, Copacetic. Do you have this story you want to continue?
Okay, so...
Like I said, I'm very sensitive, very, very sensitive.
So long story short, last year in February.
I was speaking of my cousin my friend had came over to get her hair braided before she go into work and shit
And she waitresses so they have to have a proper attire of course and their attire is you know black
Black pants and slats and you know black apron and shit like that or whatever
so therefore I put my cat in the living room and
I set my door a jar so that way I can keep an eye on my cat and I can you know
Finish my homegirl's hair and shit like that before she goes to work.
So...
It's like seeing is, do y'all want to see this shit?
Yeah, what do you have?
The picture.
Okay, show us.
Can I send it to you somehow?
you can put if you have a link to it you can put it like a link backstage in the
private chat or um or you can post it on the community board or something
it won't let me I don't even know how to work this thing
I'm gonna just show it on your screen yeah I'm gonna do this so please alright give me one second guys
like
Yeah, so when it happened, you know, like you remember me saying that
You know, I'm afraid of the dark and I'm not being funny. I'm not being sarcastic or anything
It's not I'm not pulling y'all leg or anything whatsoever. I'm I'm an open book
I'm getting ready to be 31 years old August or God's will say the same and I am still afraid of the dark
I feel vulnerable in the dark.
You remember me saying when I was telling you
about the story, I'm like, you know,
I sleep with all the lights on
and I have my fucking house lit up like a Christmas tree?
I'm not bullshitting.
I'm not.
I have to, you know, regardless of whether I didn't watch
the scary movie or not, I have to.
I feel so vulnerable in the dark, you know?
Like I said, like, you know, you should only fear God
but my mom always tells me that.
But it's hard for me to, you know, like, it just fucks with me, bro.
Like, I don't, I don't see some shit and through my 31 years of living, like, it has presented
itself more and more in the sense of, I feel like it's a sign for me and believe.
I do believe, you know, I'm seeing it, but it's like, I feel like now it presents itself
You know, yeah
Like you can tell it fucks with me because like I slept in my living room for three months fucking straight
I kept all my fucking door closed in my room and everything
I would not even go in my room unless I had to in the daytime like seriously
I slept in my living room for three months straight
Fucking scary, bro
Yeah, well, yeah, I like to sleep in my living room, too
I don't know if it's like just because it's like I like the energy here better or just like I like to like
All the people from the TV set. Hey Stens. I don't know how you would send a picture like you can show it on your screen
You can put it as your profile picture. No
Okay, just for a second
Do you have like a knockoff email like a signature or some shit? I
And when I send it to you like you'll you'll be able to see it. Just you can show like the viewers or whatever
What why be a man when you do?
There's evidence backstage I put an email address
Yeah, I can't barely hear you you're it's all messed up
Okay
Somebody says
Yeah, like you can believe thank you sassy scarlet you are entitled to believe what the fuck you want to believe that's
That's your god
I am not a liar. I have no reason. How do we know that though?
Respectfully, I'm not saying that you are a liar. You are. You have the God-given gift to believe in
what you want to believe. That's you. Nobody can touch that. That's interesting.
Exactly. Thank you, Daryl, for, for, for, for sake. I can't see.
Man, um, I can tell you this, all them fictional characters and shit, like it, Leprechaun and shit like that.
I used to be a little afraid of that shit when I was younger, but as I got older-
Leprechaun?
Yeah, like when I was younger, I that's what I was like kind of afraid of but
And I started to understand it's fictional and this and that whatever
Do you believe in Muhammad
Go ahead
What what God you believe in who's your God raise up your law who me they come
Yeah
Jesus Christ, okay, so like to you
So to you Jesus Christ is God, right, but to me God is GOD
Let me finish I am what I'm saying. No, you definitely did not I was trying to tell you what I my God
Okay, I can hear you. All right. So to you God is Jesus Christ like to me G. O. D. God is good orderly direction
So like you see in the chat nobody the guy's name is nobody every time I come on the panel
I say I'm gonna let come my brother because he believes in
Muhammad is the one true God. Okay to you. I say God bless you because you believe Jesus Christ is the one true God
And me, you know, I'll just say, uh, God bless you, psyche, because like you're my God. Now the point is is
Anybody I respect anybody's belief in a higher power that's omnisum psyche knows we've spoken about this before right psych
Yeah, and I respect you for remembering that because I speak to people about omnisum
And like you always you remembered it one day. You're like, oh, that's like the omnisum
So like now my question to you is
Why do you believe in Jesus Christ as the one true God?
That's your opinion. Now, can you give me a fact?
Okay. I don't believe in Jesus Christ.
I know him. I know he's real.
I know this.
Where did you meet him?
Seriously.
I'm getting ready to send this photo. Give me two seconds, please.
She knows Jesus Christ.
Okay, I'm waiting for this like you. What do you think?
Well, you know, it's like that is like what you want to the relationship we want to have with God is like a kind of like
Yeah, yeah, no, like a no stick not stick music knowing. Yeah, that's what said
Because I I am with somebody like that the God he's like yo school this telephone pole is my higher power
I say more power to you got it. You know what I'm saying like
Anybody's yeah, I'm looking right now. I'm looking right now a better person
Yeah, that's what's supposed to be do that was supposed to be like a religion in general supposed to like make you be
You know have hope you'll be a better person
And there's different
Ways of it, you know, yeah
As to say is if somebody's higher power is Satan and that is their God and they are a better person
Now when I say that is if they're a good person if they're a better person as we do in society
What a better person is then who am I to fucking say that Satanism for that person isn't good now if he's fucking doing things that
aren't right murdering people that's different but have we seen a lot of people who say Jesus Christ
is the one true savior and they're murdering people too right right the more people are murdered
in the name of god or religion than any other other cause um but yeah it's like uh so you know
but it's like bees that get to the semantics about you know because religions are very much the same
I'm in there. I'm in Sunday school and
None is about to hit me with a ruler. Yo, yo
Yo, I'm looking I don't see that. Huh. Yeah
No, it's okay, I'm looking for this email, but I don't see it
Jamie's in Jamie's there shout out to Jamie
Yeah, it says I sent it
Paramount hold on. Yeah
Okay, look at Jamie. She says hi. Look at that high school. That's in
Irby Feta, look at she says hello to all of you. That's so nice
Yes, I see this picture like what is what is the picture you're trying to show?
Put it on screen. Okay. What so
You see the three red arrows
Okay, hold it to the screen. We can't we can't see it
Yeah
I'm sorry, I can't it's not very clear for everybody. I'm sorry
Sorry, but yeah, yeah, but I really don't know what you're talking about though
Like what are you trying to show me in these pictures like it looks like a bunch of like
Just like a bunch of like a folded like pillows. No
It's a cloak
It's a cloak. Yeah
Okay, oh look what time said
I've never I've never heard of that
See, I I there's a lot of different rumors about that time. That's a great topic
Time always be coming with cool shit, you know
Time
in the chat
Time with like like outside of the box shit
Now did you ever figure out American football is cold football because it comes from a set of games played on foot as opposed to horseback now
That is pretty cool. But like I can you know
Kind of combat that with but rugby is not played on I
Always thought football was named football just to shove it in Britain's face
Do you know what I mean by that?
Yeah
Just you know, it's like we have the American football and then there's soccer over there, right?
It's soccer over here, correct. Yeah, like it doesn't make sense. Soccer is the worst name.
Like just call it football and why can't
American football be called American rules like the way they do Australian rules, Aussie rules. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, we could have just called that American rules and it would have been it would have been cooler
We had to name it on football and it's so stupid
Just like why we couldn't play cricket like cricket didn't become popular here because
Yeah
I'm not trying to be rude. I'm just it's hard. It's really hard to see if you could put it on your screen. That'd be like
But but let's try to get off your negativity like to get you happier
Respectfully, what do you think about? Um football soccer and
Baseball and cricket. How do you feel about I don't really care about sports
You know I'm just saying though like like if you had like if a gun was to your head and you had to like you know
No, I've rebuked that in the name of Jesus Christ saying man. Look, I'm not with all the negative stuff or whatever
I appreciate you for you know trying to carry on the conversation. So that way, you know, um my feelings are not
like, you know, disturbed or whatever, but...
Yeah, you're crying, hon.
Like, you're saying you're not with the negative stuff,
but you're crying.
I'm trying to...
I don't wanna, like, disturb your peace
or anything like that.
But you're doing that to yourself.
You're disturbing your...
Look, the thing about it is,
everything serves its purpose, okay?
You know, you never know what somebody may be going through.
I totally disagree with what you just said.
Everything serves its purpose because pedophiles
do not serve their purpose in this fucking society.
So I'm just saying, just saying that everything
does not serve its purpose.
Everything does serve a purpose.
We all have a placement.
We all have a placement in this world.
Everything does serve a purpose.
It does.
Wow, OK, no problem.
I understand why you wrote me Catholic by any chance.
Am I Catholic?
I asked you yes, but you Roman Catholic by any chance a Protestant. No, I'm I'm Christian, right non-denomination, right non-denomination
The question are you non-denomination stop getting all negative. I don't even know what that mean, honey
I don't all I know is that I am a firm believer in Jesus Christ
Jesus Christ, okay, that's you go in worship. Do you worship?
Absolutely. Okay. What like type of church do you worship at?
Not the name of the church. I'm not trying to do it. You know, I'm just asking what type of church?
Christian
Okay, right. So not Methodist, right? Cuz Methodist is the type of Christian Lutherans the type of Christian
She's not the nomination
So, so what I mean by non-denomination is you don't claim
Any type of Protestant right or Catholic?
You know like you know the difference right between Protestantism and Catholic Catholicism
Look all of these are fucking titles title
Correct. All things don't mean another fucking thing. Okay. That's what non-denomination means no title
They don't mean any anything. I agree
I agree with the faith that you have is within there's no
She's like wants to fight with me. So when you are talking about something that is that's god-given
If you I agree, honey, why are you trying to fight?
You're not the nomination for world, okay? Yeah, you're not the nomination
That's what you are you are built before you are gonna just let her go crazy your soul your spirit
Your soul is first and then your spirit and then your vessel your vessel is your body
This it does not matter
Okay, something a lot prison be alive. Oh, yeah
I agree. So you know Athens. Do you lack social awareness, bro?
Sometimes I'm just trolling brother
You know like when you got to read the room
They're like read a room bro like
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's what I just said, that's what I just said.
Hey, by any chance, are you, do you describe yourself as a girl?
Do you have two eyes by any chance?
Uh, hell yeah, hell yeah.
By any chance, do you eat eggs in the morning?
Because it might seem that you have high cholesterol.
Do you eat eggs with broccoli?
I know, hell yeah.
I'll put you back.
Hey, by any chance, do you live in Long Island?
Because I just might know that, uh, yeah.
Uh, you can tell by that horrible fucking accent of mine, right?
you're fucking scumbag dude you're fucking scumbag
hey we don't care bro let the four women she was speaking to psyche then
you're coming on here oh do you do you believe in god
oh do you believe in this bro let the woman live bro get off her neck
How are you respect respect I give him I give him a salute for that RTR. You know what that is psyche
Arthur no RTR, but it already are on read the room read the room. I'll read the room. Okay. I got you
Okay
You know that Microsoft teams was coming up. He was the one that said that skype and the other one was
He was the one that pointed out on Cinco de Mayo that skype fucking collapse that they were closing that day
Yeah, it's park guy. How's everyone in chat doing? Let's see
Let me know if you see something good in chat like if I'm missing you thing
I'm sorry if I do guys. How are you doing? Hey, sweet pea? Hey time. Jamie's Cowboys Arthur
Hope you guys having fun. We're just chilling this morning
Have a really morning stream
Go ahead and tell your story if you have the rest of your story
Oh, if you want to share yeah, I'm pretty much like you can ask me what you want to but
So you saw inside entity or you were haunted by entity or what happened like did you ever you know get rid of it or?
I've seen it or whatever it presented itself and
I try to quote unquote, in my mind, mentally,
I try to protect myself with me, always being in the light.
You know, like I said, I can't sleep with the lights off.
I feel very vulnerable.
And even at this wrong age of me being 31,
getting ready to be 31 in a couple of days,
I'm very fearful of the dark
and I'm very fearful of things that I cannot see.
And I don't mean things that I cannot see,
like as if it does not exist.
My, through my experience, I was experiencing things of that nature of paranormal before
I was even able to put it into context and tell my mom that I was scared.
My mom noticed things when I was younger and she asked me.
She said, I don't want to say my name, but she's like, what's wrong?
Why do you, it was certain things that I would do.
You know when it's time for you know
Everybody to go to sleep and shit like that or whatever like if mom if my mom will have fallen asleep on the couch
Which he did sometime like I would wait until my mom is like sleep
And I would like tuck my body in like the couch with her or whatever
And that was something that I was used to doing because you know
I was smaller, but then as I got older and stuff I couldn't do that anymore because you know
I'm a growing child. I'm getting big and shit, you know, so like around eight or whatever like seven and eight
Like that's when I wasn't able to you know tuck myself in a couch with my mom
And she hold me while I go to sleep and stuff or like my dad or whatever like when him and my mom get into it
Like he'll sleep in my bed or whatever like you know saying fucking up and go sleep with my daughters
You know he'll sleep in my bed and stuff. So I was very comfortable. I always always had the sense of physical security
You know I'm saying around me so therefore when my mom and my dad separated
and my mom had her significant other
and now I don't have that comfort of
I can sleep in my mommy bed whenever,
my dad's sleeping in my mom's bed,
my mom's sleeping in her bed
and I can sleep with my mom and my dad.
But now that she has somebody that's not my father,
I can't sleep in my mom's room.
I can't sleep in her bed.
So therefore,
me and my sister, we share rooms. My sister is one year older than me, same mom, same dad.
So my bed is on one side of the room. Then we have our, our book stand and shelf and
sheet on our desk in between her bed and my bed. So, you know, we share rooms, but just,
you know, give an example of how fearful I was, like I said, before I was even able to
Put it into context and tell my mom mommy. I'm scared something is bothering me
You know certain things like that before I was even able to speak those words
I've always had the scary like like she noticed a lot of things that I was doing like okay
Since I couldn't sleep in my mommy's bed anymore, right?
I would one time I tried to fucking sneak under her bed and hide and not hide
But go to sleep under her bed before they went to fucking sleep because she got her fucking boyfriend
I want to sleep with my mommy
They found me under the fucking bed because my mom fucking she wouldn't start looking for me
She's like, what the hell like, you know what I'm saying? So they found me under the fucking bed
She's like, yeah, you can't do you know what I'm saying? So she was talking to me and shit
So what I um did was like for me to be able to go to sleep and shit like that or whatever
I would wait, now may I remind you, me and my sister,
we shared the same room, my bed is on one side,
the book stand and the desk is in the middle,
then her bed is on the other side.
So what I would do was I would wait,
I would have my head under the covers, right?
No matter what the season was,
no matter what, you know, winter, fall, spring, whatever,
I would have my head under the covers.
and I will face the wall.
Now this is in my bed, the same room with my sister,
my sister on the other side.
I will have my head facing the wall,
my head under the covers,
no matter how hot I was or whatever.
And I will sit, I will wait.
I will wait until like, I could not go to sleep, okay?
I will wait until I know my sister is in a deep sleep.
And I will sit there and I will fucking sleep
and have my head under the covers.
Like so much of my fucking breath is hitting the wall
that it will create condensation.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, you know what condensation is, right?
So that's how serious this shit was.
So I will wait like at least an hour.
or probably more until I know my sister is in a deep sleep.
And I would squeeze on her side of the bed on the wall.
And anytime we had sleepovers, my cousin watching us
and stuff like that.
And we got all the cousins that, you know what I'm saying,
at our house or wherever at my auntie rabbit house, whatever.
I would, you know, we make palettes and stuff like that.
Everybody get a whole bunch of blankets
and we kicking and having fun and stuff like that.
It's kids and shit.
And preteens watching us or whatever.
I would literally have to be in the middle.
I could never be on the outside,
sleeping on the outside, never.
I always had to be in the middle.
If I wasn't in the middle, I have to be against the wall
and somebody on the side of me, always.
That shit is crazy dude, always.
Wow, this is crazy.
Thank you for sharing those stories.
I mean, it's like, you know,
it's kind of like you've been through a lot and...
Interesting paranormal stuff. How's the chat doing? I'm looking at the chat on my tablet right now
Hey, Samman. Anybody want to come up and say hi?
We're just having
You know, I think like I
Have to get back in therapy
My sister told me so and I know I do
But I just have to have that right connection
You know, I have to feel it like I have to know that you're not, you know reading from you know, like a prompt like you know
a script or whatever. Oh
You believe people are reading from a script in life? Yeah. No, not now. I'm saying like I
had like therapists in the past or whatever and
My most recent therapist like I have to discontinue our sessions because I just didn't really feel it or whatever
Like I have to feel a connection
Yeah, yeah, they'll basically they'll tell you like, you know, they'll ask you to like talk
And they want you to talk and it just will prompt you a little bit, but they really don't like
Tell you think that really will help you when that's a fairly thing about nothing is fake about supernatural
Nothing. Yeah, it's not fake. No, I know yeah
The guy whoever that is in the chat
And look
I'm not even gonna go there. Like seriously. I'm not like I'm not even gonna water that plant. That's it already dead
Okay, no not you
Okay, here you go, here you go, here's the link
Here we go
What do you have to say?
I did
Yeah, I would you I was reading the chat about Tim Burton and
They have a stick in London. If any of you guys in the chat in London, you know
There's a stick Tim Burton museum. Yo, I'm in London. Yo, hey, sorry. Thank you. Hey, what's up?
Alright, what's up? How you doing? So what's going on? What's up? I've got a question for you though site, but what's going on out here?
What's the story? How you doing? Are you doing ladies? How you doing? How you doing chat?
You better now what happened y'all you okay?
It's your first time on the panel. There's your first time on the panel. I get on here
Okay
So God bless God bless. She was on last night
So what's up, Sam and you good site? I would just what's going on with this biscuit stuff site with you. What's up with the
Nothing, I don't know beat it. It's like
And it's like I think it means something to you psych. I mean you could
Means absolutely nothing
About to tear me up psych. Look, I'm not I'm not I don't care, but it's like it's just so dumb
Here's the here's the retort to that
Shit hold on I'm just asking a question you feel me sorry. I got no bees
I know I'm not I'm not a son at all. I'm
Nobody hey Jamie's repeat
Mojo Jojo Katrina
I'm waiting psych with okay, it's coming. It's coming. It's gonna happen in one second. You're gonna be towards work
One second. Here it is. Hey Nancy
PERSIAN FUNKERS, PETTY, POETIC JUSTICE SAID IT CAME THROUGH WITH THE TRAIN OF SMIRK
TALKING ABOUT BISKETS LIKE SHE DID THE WORK
BUT BABY THOSE SKOLES WERE DRYER THAN TAYERON
WHERE'S THE HONEYSAUCE, GIRL IT'S GONE
YOU SAY YOU'RE THE QUEEN OF THE CREW
BUT YOUR BUTTER SLIPPED OUT LIKE IT'S DODGING YOU
Y'ALL MIGHT CHECK, MIGHT CHECK
TURN OUT TO THE CATCHAC
Thank you
Okay, it's Persia. It's Persia's song. I don't know. I made it five minutes. Go on, I need that song. I need that song.
Drop it in your server.
Goddamn Facebook
I'm pretty sure yet
I think there's a better version
This is not efficient
This is construction material
Where is the butter?
Where is the love?
Where is the soul?
Why you don't do that out of lived?
So I got a diss track again beta. That's your head different B. Damn. Are you ready for war?
I mean it was like it was a friendly like little retort to it and then it's like and then she's like, oh you use AI blah blah. Oh, yeah
Yeah, really she got really mad it was a it was a friendly it was a little like
Did you play it? Yeah, that's not even the best. That's not the best version. I think this is a better version. I'll put the better version up.
Let's see it.
Mojo, Stanley Kubrick's done. You got a Stanley Kubrick and Sidney Lumet, Mojo. Then you'll understand.
This one I like better. Hold on. This one's gonna take a little bit longer.
Juniper, Sidney Lumet, bro.
Not a woman. Oh, okay
Sike can I get the song please? Yeah, I put them on like this part
Thank you.
Where is this music coming from?
Yo, Psy cooking! Yo, Psy cooking!
Hey, Vax! Hey, Queen Vax!
Well, I get all these texts so late.
Bacaba! Bacaba!
What?
It sounds like that guy who does the, um, fucking, um, what?
Oh, god damn.
What's his name, Psyche? I can't remember.
He had that Fireflies hit in, like, 2000s.
I don't remember.
Forget it. Forget it.
Block. Thank you. I can make I can make a I can make any a I can make I'm gonna be a Sandman song to you
But but it's gonna be friendly though. I'll be friend. That's the name of the guy
You go pull over
Let's get to that. We cook.
I'm going to put you on a tarot card, too. I'm going to put you on a tarot card.
I'm going to get some tarot cards.
Put me with the red balloon.
You got some red balloons?
Yeah, bro Sidney Lumets the greatest all-time now you didn't even mention him there's a page card
No, who is this guy this can head of the drive Canadian?
Yeah, that's a school that is cool about me. Oh
What? What? What? What? What?
No, what I said was, normally it says school actors, but it says the S.O.A.
No, I'm talking about you. I'm talking about you. I remember you school.
Yeah, yeah, I was saying that it was my fault. It was the S.O.A.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I got a change tonight. It says S.O.A.
Nah.
Nah, you good. I'm talking about you.
I was wondering when you came up, I was like, don't send it.
Yeah, when you came up, you were like, yeah, what's good ladies and I was like
Yeah, yeah, I'll confuse you my fault you got the other guy that always come on
That come on
Yeah, Canada's band right now. He's he's uh, he's uh, he's another time out right now
Yeah, who's the other girl? Who was the girl right there though? What was her story? Manji? What was her story?
You know, well you I could have protect her. It's like you ain't tell me
I was telling some of paranormal stories, and she's like a little bit freaked out about some stuff, but I talked to her
Respectfully, I think her name is uh her name is uh, oh she's left
Well, I wouldn't know what was her story, you know, she's here. Here she is
Oh, yeah, Sammy you could call me Sammy. Yeah, you could call me Sam. What's up?
Um, what did you want to know?
Well, what's the story I try to I caught in late you feel me?
Um, we were speaking about um
One more so like I was speaking about like my experiences or whatever
I was telling psych about
It's like really fucking scary like seriously psych. Can you please pull up the picture? Oh
Yeah, you got a picture
It's really hard to see the picture. I mean it's like she said this picture. It's like I'm like pillows and stuff
I'm not sure
So I would rather for you to see it and then you like it's seeing is believing
I don't really too much want to like go into depth and he tell or whatever, but I'm very sensitive of
You know, can I say one thing? Hold on in the blood of Jesus? Can I say one thing in the blood of Jesus?
In the blood of Jesus. All right. I believe in God. All right before you show anything. I believe in God
I'm God-fearing or in the blood of Jesus. Okay?
Oh, okay. Now, check it out. Hold it straight. Okay. How about this psyche? Can you dim your screen on your your laptop screen, please?
Well, not your iPad or your tablet. Dim the laptop screen. So I don't I'm not able to I don't see. Hold on. Let me see. Let me see.
Oh, wait, what's this?
I'm not sure. Here. Here we go.
So how about that? Hold it. So where the glare isn't.
We can see it. I could see it. Okay, so what do you see? I see a bag. I see a bag. I see a bag
How about this? I'll get myself on the screen for you guys. Okay. No, no, you know, keep it there for one second
Okay, so if you hold it to where do you see three arrows? There should be a bottom red arrow
Yeah, I see three arrow. Yeah, I see the red. Yeah, I see an arrow
One two, I see two arrows on top of the bag and I see an arrow at the bottom of the base
But the thing about it is I was explaining to you guys how
I'm not afraid of too much of this physical world.
I don't want my life to be taken
by the hands of another man, absolutely not.
But the thing that I fear most is,
you know, from my experience.
My great grandfather, he was a hudu doctor.
You know, he practiced hudu.
You know what hudu is, right?
Yeah, I have the who-do tear who do it's like the who-do terror I have the who-do terror right here
Oh hell no, what the fuck y'all talking about man. Oh, I'm black magic
What is that site I'll be telling you I yummy yummy fuck with this black magic man. I believe in Jesus
Okay, okay, I believe in God. Yeah, I don't even I don't even like doing okay. I am I am a child of God
That's all I know
God bless God bless. I'll be telling people God bless everybody Jesus. I know Jesus. Oh
Damn, okay, so it's okay. I like that
So what happened so what what what?
So, Wudu or Wudu is not Wudu?
Wudu.
I don't know the difference from Wudu or Wudu,
but I know it's point blank that it's black magic, okay?
My mom was raised by her grandfather,
which is my great-grandfather.
They're from Tutwiler, Mississippi.
Do y'all know, okay, you know the movie Life
with Martin Lawrence and Eddie Murphy?
Yes.
That was shot in Mississippi.
You see how they was on a, that's a plantation.
So, therefore, they was deep down in Mississippi to where they had fucking outhouses to go
use the restroom and slaughter hogs and shit, and my great-grandfather would do his rituals
and shit around my mom and my aunts and shit like that.
My mom was raised by her grandfather, so they have this thing, my uncle said, he believes
So generational curses, it skips a generation.
So everything comes from maternal that you inherit.
So like most of your traits and shit like that or whatever.
So like, it skipped my mom's generation
and my uncle believed it, you know.
My uncle believes it it fucks with me, you know, one thing I'm not I'm not a liar and I will never lie to you
That's all I got. It's the truth for you unless I'm trying to say my own ass. That's all I got
You know, so there's no reason for me to lie and I will never play with anything like this
I've had so many things happen like
Like you like what the fuck like you didn't you didn't you didn't go to church for it
You didn't try to you know you go to church you can go to church and stop and holla and all this other shit does not matter
Yeah, but this uh, I'm not even trying to I don't know you like I shot it to you like I'm not judging you
I mean, I'm you feel me you could you know pray to you know pray something there's ways uh, there's ways uh, you know
Are you uh dealing with that shit?
Stop giving it. It's not giving it power too. Don't give it power
Can't give it power. That's the problem. What y'all do y'all give it power
Yeah, that's why I don't disrespect and look things like that feed off of energy. Yeah, look look no disrespect
It's I could tell you I tell site site. This is a
Wait, I'm sorry y'all
Sassy scarlet. I see two eyes and nose in a mouth
That's how I don't even
She's not in the picture. She's not like some shapes and stuff. Yeah
know I saw a little bit of it it's like you know but you have to kind of use your imagination a little bit but
Yeah, but that's also like we also make shapes in our our head
We like we like to make sense of like different things, but it could be like a pareidolia or something
Is that what it's called pareidolia? Like over it's like you
Say like
That's perfect example say if you see a splash of water on a cement or special paint on a wall
I could look at it as a different image and you could look at it as a different image
But the same shit is how you bring things
Mm-hmm, but I tell you say that's what site. No, dude. No disrespect to you site
That's why I don't do the terracotta readings. You might joke around I'm even play with that shit
That's why I say I respect your channel. I do what you do. That's what I say
Just respect me you feel me and that's what we have an understanding. I fuck with you
I'm not bashing what you do, but with me
I don't mess with them tarot cards. No, not everybody not everybody agrees with that spiritually or you know
Religiously, so I don't push it on anybody. It's like
And I respect that site and that's about to tell you and I respect that site. Yeah
Hello
I'll put her on mute for a second. Hold on
There we go. I put her on mute
Okay, the cats. Hi guys. How are you doing? Yeah, so I found a mute while she's talking to her
right after the cash out
Send them to make me laugh
Put on you psych put on you psych put on you I tried I tried
I did I did I did
Don't have her mom on these panels man
Yeah
so
Anyway, we're all good. So what are you going on doing the live soon?
That's my mom called that was my mom calling me and shit or whatever
God bless your mom. God bless your mom. Thank you, but that's like that maternal instinct, you know
That's one you felt something you felt something
I mean, I, I'm the youngest or whatever, but I'm very, I'm very fucking, like, emotional
shit, dude, like, seriously.
Like what are you how you found sight you've been around
I used to come to his page and just listen to them speak about God and shit like that or whatever and
You know the energy was right and shit. So eventually I just got alive with him stuff
So you don't got a channel or nothing. Do you just a challenge that just I do
That's a sight
Put yourself on mute. Put yourself on mute.
Yep, this is not supposed to be forever.
Okay, I gotta talk to you about something very important.
Uh-oh.
Sight, put it on.
Yo, send me, send me.
Send me.
Yo.
Sight.
I wanted to ask you.
Why didn't you call the people?
How'd you call the people?
I
Come through right
Yo, you want to come through soft or hard?
I don't fucking know what's wrong with this shit
Yeah, can you guys that question again? It's it's good now. We hear you
I don't think you can hear shit
It's probably in and out of connection. I'm always driving during
Yeah, we hear you now. So say it now. We hear you now
I was just curious how you came up with the name sandman when I first heard it
I thought people were calling you like sandman like mariano reverie, you know like the sandman
My son is good teacher. It's like a it's a playoff of the Sandman. It's the same man
So my name, you know, everybody know my name
Yeah, so I put Sam
Nice the set that's good shit like Mariano Rivera, you know, I don't know if you're a Yankee fan
But the he's the fucking closer, you know, he'd be putting people to fucking bed close. He closes shit. Yeah
That's a sassy
Mr. She's just like that
And she bailed me out too, so it stuck with me she bailed me out out of fucking jail nigga
So shout out to send out to my son. It's damn
Fat she love me
Mr. Sandman bring me a dream
Yeah, yo, she's I was like, oh shit. I got me a soul. Oh, yeah
She was mad cool, bro. No lie, bro. Like harder gold. That's when I knew color ain't nothing
Color ain't shit. She she she narrow judgment. I was uh, I was from the
This whole side is no good, what about the other side?
No gas nothing. Okay. Okay
I try yo, I got hop off I tap in if I tap in your fight
Okay, thank you, Sam and thank you. Thank you
Put them songs in the server so I can share okay, okay, I will thank you
The last one I think the last one is a little bit better than the first one though. Okay, I'll do last one
Yeah, we could say man. I know you can read it shit
Now fuck with you school. Oh
Yeah, yeah, it's a salute. I'll be on your page and shit you and Ron be you and Ron a funny man
So Jamie wanted me to share this photo. This is a photo from like I guess the accident
But she says she's seen the skin walker in this photo. So let me see. I'll put it on for you guys to see
Thank you. I gotta go too. I'll be back. I gotta go
Okay, it's hard to see but the guys look up real closely that like what's circled right there. You can see like a face
It says not Louise
Anyway guys, wow 47 people in the chat. If anyone wants to come up right now, you're welcome up
Otherwise, I might I don't know if I might wrap it up in a few minutes
It's you're a bit on for about an hour and a half. I can come on a little bit a
Little bit later, but how are we doing back sins? Hey, or how are you doing? Hey, Nicole? Hey chibi chibi. Hey everybody
Sweet Pea, Jamie's Cowboy, Sassy Scarlet.
Do you see the face there?
It looks, I saw it close up.
You zoomed in, it's creepy.
Yeah, go ahead and try to zoom in.
You can see this kind of scary ghostly face right there.
I'm sorry, maybe I'll try to get this picture
zoomed in on a little bit.
But yeah, I wish I could zoom it in there.
But pretty cool though.
This is trippy, scary.
There's one more okay, let me get the other one hold on
I was a mod in the land of tarot trees
She was Satan's ex, with that fiery stare.
Told me my rising sign, like she actually
I'm stuck in hell
She's a public figure. Yeah, she has 25,000 subscribers. So, uh, yes, I would consider her a public figure
Anyway
Very use
Hmm
No, she's not she has a she's not talking to me anymore. I'm actually my name is blocked in her chat
I think I might use
It's tobacco. It's fucking tobacco. These are these backwoods I'm smoking. They're pretty terrible.
Got it. Thank you.
Oh, this is when I wake up in the morning. I'm in my boxers. I'm just pedaling with tricks over here.
Please it was a joke. It's called a joke. Nobody gets my sense of humor. I
Said it's 25,000 subscribers
We're gonna have a very well slip and slide which is a joke that I've used another channel successfully
But it didn't work on her channel. Okay, I
Love you. I might miss you
anyway
I'm not really a creep
Well
Not that big of a creep
Yeah, thank you mama Maria mama Maria she got my back. I
Think it's a cute song though. Oh my goodness gracious
Need to get a fleek home
There we go, hey, babe
little baby little tricks here hi tricks how are you guys doing I hope you guys
are having a great what is it Thursday or today's uh yeah Thursday is it
Thursday oh wow yeah the week is just flying by huh here with tricks just
Little cuddle bug. He likes to sleep with me. Hey, babe
You want to come up with panel? I don't know. Maybe I'll take a little
Afternoon nap. It looks like the chats calm down a little bit. Hey guys, they was a devil get the hordes
He'd have a card sure sweepy. I have these new if he's new it's new deck. Hold on. This is called leaving your own magic
The really cool deck like a little Oracle deck
What's the zombie footage the Norse been here the Norse lurky's coming inside, but she's like supposed to be outside right now
She's been outside a lot here. Oh, but uh Norse been inside
She's not missing
Okay
Yeah, I got a bit and I have another deck on the way. It's has what they call a cat full of spiders by Christina Ricci
This is the believe you're a magic Oracle deck. It's got some cool cards in it. Okay, so
you got first you got this one says escape this it says come home to yourself
so maybe like sit like that read a book and escape and you'll actually come home to yourself right
but we have we have also mirror it says treat your body like the palace it is
Okay, think about all the wonderful things the body is capable of and can do it. This is that amazing body we have, right?
And what else do we got for you?
It's a library. It does take control of your own narrative.
So don't let yourself be puppeteered. Like this channel. Nice people.
Thank you, Sony. Oh, I do I have the labyrinth deck. I have to dig that out. I do have a labyrinth deck.
So you guys want me to get the labyrinth deck? I will look for it tonight, okay?
I've been cleaning out my bedroom,
getting it organized finally, finally, finally, finally,
did all my laundry.
Anybody else want some cards from the stick?
I need to plug in, I think I forgot to plug in my tablet.
You're welcome.
Yeah, Emma's a decent tarot reader.
Yeah, I've been doing it longer than she has been,
but yeah, she's,
Definitely got a system down and she does great readings, but
These are free readings by the way that I'm doing if you would like, you know, $10 reading
I will do like a longer reading
Similar to how she does I just haven't had a donation for a tarot reading in a little while
So maybe you just see the short ones, but I do do longer ones. Okay universe. We're all just stardust
Yeah
I'm not and I would not put down anybody or anything like that or
And so I'm not trying to compare anybody like I love people will try to compare
Oh, you're this is a better read will have different
Compatibility of different readers on on tick-tock. They love my readings because it's a fast-paced thing here. It's like people want longer readings
And I will offer them for
For a donation
But otherwise, I'm happy to do free readings that they are quicker, right?
So anyway, I should do I should do like longer collectives for the chat and stuff like that, but hi, babe
My little kitty cat. Oh, he's easy soft
This cat's very sweet.
This is Little Tricks all.
Tricks all spruced up.
I can read for you, Jamie.
Okay, let's pull some of these for Jamie.
Jamie has castle it says it's time for healing not war, and I think that's a really good one for you Jamie
Time for healing not war. I know like you might
Be upset with this woman, you know the car accident stuff, but I think it's best to
Maybe forgive
That's on your own time this one says villain you can always rewrite the story
Okay
Villain you can always rewrite the story, okay?
Maybe then we have evil queen you deserve sugar not salt, okay?
Yeah, I like Emma too. I mean it's like I'm on say is I miss Emma and you know she kind of like
Unceremoniously
Especially since I was her first member on her show. I was her mod for several months and
Then she was actually my first interview on this show. She did about an hour and a half interview and it was a really great interview
hmm
Then she ended up like I invited her back on the show and she basically
Said oh, well, I don't like your show because you know you get drunk and you know you fall asleep on it sometimes and and then
But it's just a very insulting like in front of everybody on her server
so I left her discord server and then I addressed it on my show and then
She didn't like what I said or something like that and you know started blocking me
But now that I did some friendly raids to her show. I had some readings since then
I had like a two readings or something since then but now I'm blocked on every account
Used to be Nicholas Cage and Elon Musk in her chat. She loved it. She's like I brought a lot of fun to the show
I think and
But it was good that I like you know
She on friend or she blocked me or whatever because then I started doing my own show and stuff because I did like you know
Dedicate a lot of time to her show
but anyway
Not even I
Introduced her to bunch of her mods and you know her mods will turn against me like people tend to do
Oh, these leezies. Oh my gosh
Yeah, it's like a weekends has been sleeping a little bit too much lately. I've been sleep
There we go
That's easy's off. Yeah, I can't please
What is the purpose of fleas that are too annoying annoying cats and stuff? It's like so pointless
Little bloodsuckers
Anyway guys, I love you guys. It seems like it's uh, I
Don't know. I think maybe I said I didn't pin the link or something like that. Is anyone else want to come up?
Yeah, let's see. Maybe I'll pin the link. Hold on one second.
Yeah, there's no link here you go guys. I'll pin it. I'll pin the link. Here you go.
Okay
Okay, I know Mike. This is like way slow. Okay, take the watch later. Come on
Kind of want copy right now
They copy today copy today
That'll make me up a little bit I have some my jack in the box left
Jam tomorrow jam yesterday, but never ever jam today
Oh, okay, let's see what I got. Yeah, everything's on members only pretty much. Okay, here we go
40 watching almost two hours, okay
Here the link is gonna be pinned. Oh, there you go pin
Did it work yep
You guys you like the you like the member icon it looks pretty good I
Can also I have like, you know, there's things that the
chat can use
See we have the ghost we have the old lady
The weird smile see the emojis these are like a member emojis
Um, thank you guys for liking the stream
Make sure you can you get a wrench if I get to know you better
maybe
Lavender oil for the fleas. Yeah
Yeah, you like them there. They're pretty good. There's like a lot of cool ones
I did like I haven't the maximum amount I can have up of them now
But yeah, they look pretty good on this screen
Guys, did you see the other day? We had daddy big news on he's a really cool guy. I don't know if you saw that
that show but
I'm gonna have to read read
Edited a little bit because we got poor mom at the end of the interview, but he was a really cool guy
I want to thank him for being on the show. Hopefully he'll come back to the show. Hey, babe
He's been posting a little bit of stuff. Hey, babe
I think he's on right now too if you guys want to go say hi to him
It's daddy bigness
His name is Andrew. He's uh, he's working out
He's a powerlifter and he was nice enough to come on the show the other day that my request
No, we have a nice nice nice audience right now
You like the BKG one?
Yeah, I got one in my tattoo.
Oh, Arthur wants to rest.
Hey, Summer, how are you?
Everyone feel free to come on up,
make some mistakes in my hair.
I'm a little bit, oh.
I'm a little bit off balance lately, hold on.
I've been a little bit off balance
because my ears kind of clogged up in it.
You know how it sometimes that takes off
your body balance a little bit.
Arthur hey Arthur, maybe I will consider wrenching you in the future
But not when you remember Arthur you like we criticize me and they mean things to me as the mod and I can't have
Mods saying that stuff. Hey, baby. Oh, baby
My little Trixie
I can see my bony legs today look very bony
Okay, hi summer. Hey everybody. Hey babe. Hey babe
My baby and my babe
The good little kitty my little kitty cat little tricks
Hi
My little kitty cat
Well, you know, I love beat up and it's like it, you know, I don't even want I shouldn't even say her name
She'll like starts beating. I can't even say her name. So
Better not I guess not mention it so come here excuse me up biscuits again
Didn't flee to the floor. Well, but you know, there's not like so many of them. I and I do vacuum ups. So
No, she I hope it's just joking around but she like she says, you know, she's just very insulting and saying like all these
Yeah, that's in shambles
I don't know if you if you hear what she's saying like, you know, and she doesn't think I'm listening
She doesn't say very nice things
But...
Everything I do, it's taken the wrong way.
Like, I try to do, like, the good nature, like, little song.
And then she's like, oh, you're so stupid
because you're so stupid and uncreative.
You can't do anything besides create AI songs.
And everyone else thinks they're pretty funny.
And like, well, maybe not everybody,
but I'm not like a talented musician.
So that's what I have available to me.
Other people maybe are talented musicians.
She can rap or whatever.
Hi, ETC tabs
Ah, I don't know sweep you a lot like last I thought she was mad at Jim Nick
And you know Jim Nick is just like a very sweet person like so I don't know
Couple copies
Yep, they need a couple coffees
Are you sitting in front of tea in front of the front of the computer mr. Tricks?
Hi
Just sitting in front of the computer, okay
I've been getting a lot of door-to-ash lately
Couple copies
Might as well not even get the extra shot because they don't even put it in I don't think so. Let's get the regular
Yeah, my teeth I had these the jack-in-the-box tacos. Let me see
I don't think there's a deal anywhere, deal, or coffee.
Don't condone us, five dollars off, oh, Ziggy's 20% off.
Okay, let's do Ziggy's.
I can get a butter pecan latte, a turtle, I get 20% off.
Doesn't really come to that great of a deal.
Hey summer, you about to go to the gym cool. I go work out like I woke up kind of early this morning
Hi, babe. Oh
Okay, I
Do have some weed it maybe I'll smoke a little bit weed on camera and pass out, you know, where's my weed?
Here it is
Oh yeah, so Dunkin' Donuts has been 20 bucks and I don't want to spend 20 bucks on donuts and coffee.
Actually, maybe that will take me till tomorrow. Maybe that's not a bad deal. I have a couple coffees then.
It was a place called Phil's, and what do they have?
They have like a honey haze, most liked by about a honey haze.
That looks pretty good, a large one, okay.
With creamy oat milk, okay.
And what else do they have?
Blueberry Breeze, ice coffee, rose, sweet harmony.
What's this one?
Cold brew muddled met cinnamon and oat milk. Okay, you got a large one of those. Okay
And three dollars off 14, okay, so I get something free 31 minutes delivery time, okay jalapeno cheddar bagel
With cream cheese
Where does this come to
I had a good copy last night from the
from Jack in the box
I don't know, Bita was kinda mad at everyone, I don't know, but let's be careful, I have to be careful about the...
I don't think she wants to be mentioned. Okay.
Thank you guys. Thank you guys. So there's a typical clatch coffee and they have some it looks pretty good. Let me see
Hot chai latte hot flavor. Okay. Hot creme brulee latte
This looks pretty good
It's expensive
Okay
It's 11 a.m. Tommy was in the shower. Okay, this needs to be plugged in I think okay
There are we charging
Oh, please bought baby cheek check again. Who cares? I can just name it whatever I want to it's actually a really cool lettering
It doesn't even it looks like you could say anything
I don't really care
Because actually I still I still like her
Can't get rid of me so easy
Okay, well, maybe I will
Try to find a good deal smoking tiger coffee and bread
Five miles away. What do they got?
Chai lattes banana milk latte. Yes, that's what I want
Banana milk large
Mmm more sweet
Okay, what else they got? Sweet corn latte a chai latte
And I can take a photo of it and get credits
Okay, I take the best photo. I don't know I
Want extra hot hot large
Chai latte that's like there's coffee in that right yep coffee
More sweet
Okay
Delivery, okay, much as a
Can you
Oh free express
This is too expensive, I'm not paying you like $20 for coffee, you know Aussie tattoos. Yeah
42 people in chat awesome guys. Well, let me see what can I do? I'll do some hoodoo cards for the chat
I'll do like three of these hoodoo cards
This is a message for everybody
Because it's nice deck though, it's got a nice big deck
What's speaking to us? Starbucks is expensive, but it's like I was looking at other places like with deals and stuff like that
I think I might do the donut place because I can get at least like donuts have $5 off the dough nuts and
Then I'll be like off enough basically through for the night. Okay
Okay, who do okay, so we got
Okay, what do we got here?
Okay
Some kind of communication has been slow eight of six reverse eight of wands reverse. There's been some kind of slow
Communication waiting for something to come through and then but also it gets this ace of coins
You're waiting for this luck
Or this new financial opportunity. Also. We have dr. Grant. So I'll read dr. Grant. He looks like he's the
hermit
The doctor grant the hermit it says
But he Jesus I would withdraw to desolate places and pray
So it says plant duckweed said dr. Grant is shown in solitude picking herbs and roots in the swamps of Louisiana
Dr. Grant was a Protestant conjure doctor from New Orleans
Unfortunately the details of the death are unknown by the time Zora Neil Hurston interviewed dr. Grant others in their 30s
Many conjure doctors were using herbs and other supplies from catalogs
Dr. Grant however was a proud swamper who preferred to do things the old-fashioned way by gathering what he needed in the wild
Dr. Grant reminded Hirston of a few critical but often forgotten lessons.
Believe in one's limitless power, petition spirits unequal to man,
know more than one way to get a job done,
and acknowledge that no two people or two jobs are alike.
Because a remedy that works for one person may not work for another.
Dr. Grant was highly sought out for his abilities,
and in some cases was paid more than $100,
an exorbitant amount of money for the time.
When Dr. Grant appears in a reading, it may indicate the necessity for some time alone
to recharge.
Specifically, it may recommend solitude or nature to reflect and listen.
The most important now than ever is we're constantly accessible to others via technology.
While this may be convenient, it is also a tremendous burden for we have little time
to clear our heads and just be without earbuds blasting music in our ears as zillion advertisements
Or social media alerts hanging for us to engage with the world again. They won't stop
So you must make a conscious decision once in a while to make it stop
Let's be clear this card is not about sitting in a park for a few minutes looking at pretty trees flowers or a squirrel
Before you get back online. No, it's about considering the essence of that tree those flowers and the squirrel
And how you're connected to them. It's about perceiving the inner relationships of all things to the other
the extraction of power from fundamental reality. For it is from the
comprehension of source that knowledge may be accessed and distilled. Remember,
if you take something from Mother Nature, don't forget to give something
biodegradable to her and to all creatures in return.
This card may also indicate that you're seeking knowledge and you're ready to take things to the next level. It's time to seek guidance from a worthy teacher.
If you receive doctor grants and are reading consider the following. Do you understand the importance of alone time?
Maybe it would be better to stay home tonight. Silence is golden. Focus on finding out the truth.
Be in the world, not of it. Pay more attention to your guru or spiritual counselor.
Did you really consider the advice you received about that issue?
It's okay to take a break from him, her, them, or that to reevaluate things.
Meditate more, follow your inner voice.
Hope you like that.
That was a nice inspirational card.
Um, let's see.
Rupert Snowcones?
Yeah, so let's have a look at the donuts, please.
I'm, uh, kind of feeling like donuts are the way to go today.
Because it's 25 bucks, but then you get like a few copies and I'll be able to get $5 off. So
the Dunkin Donuts
Dunkin $5 off 25
okay, so what I can have a
Few copies I guess and
Okay, get a box of the
Hapa does then
Okay, Boston cream, a couple of those.
Glazed, jelly, one, two, three, four.
Shrubbered frosted with sprinkles
and a vanilla cream, okay?
And then I can have an iced macchiato,
a large regular, whole milk.
Okay
If it's a caramel in there
Ice macchiato original blend coffee hot, okay
Large original blend, okay
Okay
She comes to like 20 something okay 20
Okay, I
Mean it comes out to some exorbitant amount five dollars off
Let me see
I'm sorry guys. I'm trying to I'm trying to like, you know, I'm smoking pot and I'm kind of like
Necessity of caffeine right now, but I'm looking for like a good deal and it keeps being too expensive
How are we doing, guys?
Okay, Vietnamese iced coffee.
Now that I like.
You can have this.
Vietnamese iced coffee with the caramel.
Okay, $7.
What else can I get?
The Americana Bull, which is like scrambled eggs, okay
How much is it 20? Okay, now
The discount
Oh my god over $40. I'm sorry guys
Hey, hey, man. How are you doing guys? Hey, Ilya?
40 people in chat, huh?
So
Let me know what you guys would like to do
Okay, I guess I guess I'm gonna go for the city's coffee 20 bucks
Junkie James
Gosh
It's gonna bite the bullet I got some I got some discounts a couple days in a row, so
It's gonna be the best deal
Free express delivery sounds good under 20 bucks. That's fine. Let's do it
Successful, okay got coffee on the way guys
So how are we doing what else do we want to talk about today so
Yeah, let's not focus on the drama that's been going on. It's just been like, you know
Not very interesting. I like I like getting along with people. I like happiness. I like, you know
I don't want to be cheesy about it, but I really do like
Just like getting along and just not
Have it too many problems and
The love and it's like so it's like when I get keep when I get taken off that I
I don't like it and it's like I don't like to be pulled out of my loving self or like, you know, because I am a loving person and
It's like I feel like I'm getting a tag and I sometimes like take me out of my own energy. Oh my gosh, excuse me
Throw some stuff away
Okay
I got a lot of my laundry done
There are a few panel guests here as the same size as the ladies you see.
Yeah, so I'm trying to clean up my area a little bit. I have my cars, a lot of cars all over the
place, not all over the place, but I need to put them in their boxes and stuff.
But I'm slowly getting these organized I am
There
So if you guys see my tiktok, I have a really exciting tiktok too. I do really fast readings on the tiktok
It's a little bit different from this show
But I think you guys, if you like the fast-paced readings,
I do have like, you know, a CB is over there
and I think I've seen Reality Nancy there
come into the chat.
And so I just do them like maybe like an hour a day.
Just go on and it's like, you can,
people send like little roses and stuff.
You can send like, it's like a lot more like,
you know, interactive in certain ways,
but it's kind of different.
Yeah, the copy is gonna be yours soon.
Maybe I'll drink the coffee and then we go on to tick tock or something. Okay, so let me have a look at
This one through the laundry something went through the laundry, okay, let me see. Yeah, I pull my
Close out of the dryer and put it on the bed. I'm bringing blanket over. Oh my gosh. Okay. I'll bring a blanket over. Okay
Hey Rudy, this is Rudy
Ah
Look at this blanket I have finally washed it. Oh
Do I look weird? Okay
Yeah, so coffee is gonna be your suit then I'll wake up a little bit. Hey J dog. How are you? What are we talking about chat?
Oh, well, I think TikTok is like,
it's just like a different kind of website where,
I mean, I'm actually like doing a lot of readings.
I think Otto was back,
so Otto was trying to come on the other day.
I don't know if it was the real Otto or it was the fake Otto,
like, because there was a porn bombing Otto that came on too.
But, like I tell wasn't him,
and it's a different porn bombing.
Hey, Dingo, how are you?
It's a beautiful day. I'll show you my view hold on a second. I'll put open my windows a little bit. Let's air in
Purple curtains
And see my nice view now that my house is a little bit cleaner I don't mind showing
A little bit messy because there you go. See?
Looking a little bit cleaner, huh?
I've been vacuuming. It's my little
Mama Maria wants to be a mod
Let's see. I'll see how easily I can reach it in this tablet
Your big key account is banned. Oh, no, did I ban I don't maybe I don't know why you got banned
I'll look into my
My YouTube studio for that though. Let me see
Okay, yeah, it's gonna be like this you have to go community moderation
My standard moderators.
Okay, so who's banned?
Okay.
Hi.
So there's a lot of people that are banned, okay.
Swamy, OG, Charlie, Psyche's address.
I mean, I can unban some of these people.
Arsenio, I mean, there's a lot of people that are banned,
Vicky we're looking for, right?
I don't see a Vicky yet.
Oh, here it is.
Okay, Vicky, why'd you get banned though? I'm wondering why you got banned
Free them all no because a lot of them are like our docks is stuff
Guys by the way, I got accepted is that Amazon influencer like you basically you can go search for the Amazon influencer program
And apply if you have a channel because I just put in my YouTube channel and it was like you're eligible
And so now I can make a good influencer page
I can make videos for like Amazon products and like you know products I buy and stuff like that and reviews and
Then put it on my page and then you know
And that's that's a really cool thing. So yeah
And like a lot of people are banned, but it's like
The people that I see banned have been pretty rude, I think.
You went to a cool, I am banned a few people.
It was morning at 3.45, it was weird,
almost chilly, I was also wearing your shirt
all the way open.
Yeah, I saw Tommy James with shirtless
on B-Diz yesterday, all right?
Ooh, I got a good hit.
Ooh.
The Amazon pay you or give you free stuff.
I think that you can get an affiliate,
like if you like, you can link products
that you like and stuff like that
and maybe get an affiliate stuff you review.
Yeah, I know about like I think the top reviewers probably gets this stuff, too
You know like I know that I've I wish I would have like you know since the beginning of Amazon
Reviews of like everything I bought that bought a lot of stuff from Amazon over the years, right?
Yeah, and so
But yeah, I think they get some free stuff occasionally, right?
But on Amazon, I have like
Thousands of of ebooks. I have like thousands of video. I mean, it's like there's so much stuff
I got for free on Amazon like that doesn't the free ebooks. I probably like 10,000 in my library
That's why you breathe you break your jailbreak stuff by Amazon fire six. Yeah
So
How's my good my phone is charging it seems okay good
I just have to back all over my table.
Otherwise, it would be looking kind of better.
I have some issues and put this in there.
Okay.
My table is a mess, it is a mess.
It is full of tobacco, it's got,
but I gotta organize it a little bit.
There we go.
There, that's better.
Can't wait for the coffee to get here, then I'll be in a better mood
Okay, I do have
Yeah
This tobacco didn't quite work out like I wanted to oh here. It's got wet. It's one got wet
They don't sell Swisher sweets anymore because it has the word sweet and if they don't sell
Black and mild so that has the word mild and so they're gonna have to rebrand if they want to continue
Okay, the food is on the way or the coffee's on the way
Yeah, come up on panel Tommy you can you know yell at me
Who's gonna jump up who's I think the link the link is pinned
They don't want to come up or I have this book called this book will change your life
You're enjoying. Okay. Let's go
This has funny things to do every day though, so this one says dark storm clouds
were gathering. It says masturbate at 1356 to the following fantasy.
His women, dark storm clouds were gathering over the Alpine mountain tops as Emma finally
reached the refuge.
Where were the others?
Where was her husband, Edward?
Perhaps they had fallen behind and taken the safe track back toward St. Paul the Clerks
and civilization, she wondered.
Well, there is no point in panicking now.
Night was falling fast and she would spend it here all alone at the mercy of these peaks.
Exhausted, she entered the deserted cabin and barely had time to strip off her drenched
The thermal sleeping bag that Edward had thoughtfully given her, for their sixth anniversary before the deep slumber overtook her naked body.
As the moon retreated from the inhospitable horizon, strange and fitful dreams came upon her.
She tossed and turned in the night, her feverish brow victim to wild imaginings.
Oh, here we go.
Yo, what's up, psyche? How you doing, homie?
What's up today, doc? How are you?
Chillin chillin man. How about you another day in this paradise?
Another day
How's it going like what we had beat us yesterday? Did you see it in something happened to beat us yesterday?
What it was just confusing
You beat us just a fucking train wreck man. I think honestly, that's why everybody goes to beat us
You ever see like a train wreck or like a bad crash like on the side of the road and you just can't stop looking at it
That's what beat us is
That's a leader
She's just a train wreck waiting to happen that everybody wants to just go see what happened and then everybody just leaves
Nobody likes her. Nobody gives a shit about her. She gets the spoiled 50 year old brat who has two cats don't have kids two felt marriages
Let's talk that I don't want to I don't want to make these words. I don't want to I don't want to talk bad
Bro, she saw she talks all kinds of shit about you, bro
She talks so much shit about you and then when you you know you you attack back
She's like how dare you even talk back to me like this and that but like you can't defend yourself
But she wants to attack you and call you names and be disrespectful and and say you're you know
I'll count you know, I didn't want to say the stuff she said to you, but
But I don't really understand why like I didn't like it ever attack her or any of that
Like she's mad because other people have attacked her or something like that on my show maybe but like that's like, you know
She fights with people on her show just like that.
She kicks off people like fast and she criticizes me
for like not having people on or kicking people off
or certain person or this person.
Yeah.
The whole thing about it is this is your show.
You could have whoever you want on here.
You could have, you could ban whoever you want.
You could have whoever you want.
Nobody could tell you what to do with your show
just like you can't tell her to do her show.
So she should just leave your show alone.
Vice versa. She should just tell you a psyche as long as you're making money you ain't hurting nobody
You ain't doing nothing wrong
Have fun make your money and that's what you've been doing. I don't say we've been doing anything wrong
I honestly haven't seen you do shit wrong psyche and that's me personally that has nothing to do with bias against beta
I was friends with beta beta turned her back on me. You know, she called me a cuck. She called me
Simp for whatever reason for whatever reason she just called me all kinds of names the way she get to you for
And I've been nothing but nice to that girl nothing but nice for and then that's why I switched up on her because she turned on me
Same way she get to you psyche for no reason
Well because it was like for the first like three months
It was like there was like never even a bad like a negative experience with her
It was like it was just all friendly and like happy and like and it's like I don't know why I didn't see the other side like
Like until after a few months and then it's like and then it's like I haven't seen like the nice size since then it's like
Yeah, she'll never be nice again. She will not be nice again
I'll tell you that the nice part you saw it. It's gone dead and gone
You might see little glimpse of it glimpses of it here and there like maybe one or two days
But then she'll go back to the way she was
Which is this the evil part? She's just a bad person man like I mean I wish I could say otherwise for a minute
Don't want nothing bad about her. I don't wish anything portable about her. I just wanted to be a better person
Ah Tommy
Would you know her for three months on the internet and she's
There's nothing worse dude you look really weird like with the head shaved or whatever you got going clefty
Bro, why don't you find your shirt on bucking like that? Why do you have your shirt?
Take your shirt off I'll take my shirt off right now
No, you got no neck, you got no neck, you got no
No conversation conversation
Okay, so you're a pencil neck. I got a thick big old neck. You're a pencil neck snap like that
Yeah, you look creepy. We look like a straight predator by dude predator look at you bro
You're what a cowboy hat. Where's your horse? You don't even have a horse
Are you trying to hide that receding hairline pull your hat off. Let's see that line
Let me know when you're done being triggered
and
Shaved his whole head to hide how it's bad his hairline is I'm beautiful bitch look at my full head of air
38 years old what you want bit 28 you're 38. You're like 38, bro
They believe don't hit but
Those drugs bro, just stay away from them, bro
You know what okay wait well I will do drugs every day to the day. I die than to be like you
Why do you like drugs Tommy? Why do you like drugs?
My mind
As I'm sitting in a house, you want me to go show you the car?
You rent a room!
You don't even own your own house!
You
So this guy leeches off a senior citizen
He knows nothing about me because I would never let this guy be my friend friend by the way my friend be
You want me? You sound like a little old. Picture a wife. Picture a wife, bro. You want enough.
Take off. He wants me to take off articles, articles to close. He wants to ask me about blood type.
You have it a half one of a button. So if you're not scared, he's taking it off.
You want to see, I was just on a shower stream on Beatles yesterday. You want to see me naked so bad.
Pay more attention, faggot. Oh my god, this guy's really gay.
And everybody here in chat knows that I regularly kick it with no shirt. Why don't you take your shirt off faggot?
Want me to say that's how we test a clothing?
You in your chat, you notice when I start roasting him. He just bugs out
Like a fucking autistic kid
So like what you can't hear that you think that's gonna stop the people from here and we talked about how fucking much you suck
Yeah, as I sit in a home guaranteed. I make more money than you do
Why don't have any kids? Hold on. I don't hold on. I don't have any kids. What a burn that one hurt
He would
You're that little man like why like
You're little
You're not six foot. You're not you're not the same size as me. You're not the same size. There's no fucking way
Oh, yeah, when you're done being triggered watch some of my IRL streams with me next to known other streamers
Maybe you'll get a better idea how tall I am other than that you're you're way off with the five three, buddy
Yeah, okay, you know what do you have a tape measure in that garage? I'm not gonna measure myself for you
Also my a my yeah, please no do it
Measure yourself. This is so funny. He's like
Let me know when you're done autistic, baby
Hold on shut the fuck up retard. Oh, yeah
Just checked my driver's license again. Looks like I'm still six feet tall there too.
What a retard. Like make believe don't hit. But you are actually a fucking predator. When
you leech off a senior citizen that makes you a predator and he has the look too. My driver's license
Wow
I'm six foot two
Like that's gonna stop you
That's gonna stop you from getting rocked
Okay
Ha ha ha ha
Oh my god
You're so funny
You're goofy dude, you are a goofy
It's almost kind of funny. You know, you know what, J-Dog, listen, you're kind of one of those types. It almost hurts to make fun of you because it's like making fun of a recharge.
Look at him. He's like
I'm not a retard showing my ID like you
Let me know when you're done
Retard showing his fucking government ID
So get your screen shots. Hey, everybody get your screen shots. Oh, my God. And he thinks
I'm going to go run around like a monkey showing personal, uh,
Show proof, show proof, show proof, show proof, show proof, show proof, show proof, show proof,
There's your dog, you're an artist, you're gay, but you don't know how.
Make-up shit by the way homeless as I sit in a house
Back on the drugs
You'll be a fucking retard just the same way you
Let him calm down for a second before I go back to the actual point
Good
Dude finally what the fuck psyche I've been backstage for like two minutes
I'm sorry. What is this? What is this?
How much is a netflix?
How much is a netflix subscription, Psyche? How much?
It's like $12 or something. How much is it guys?
I paid you like 250 so that should give me a whole fucking year if you don't have to leave me backstage like a fucking prick
I'm sorry. First and foremost
Came on to say something. Did you see on bloggers stream last night? My god
insane
Like that dude insane. I don't fucking like it dude
Yeah, I mean, yeah, yeah, yeah, he's a great
This is like taking a baby like again, he's dream was like shooting fucking straight dope into the neck like
I want to make sure we saw the same stream what stream he's talking about blogger blogger
Where he begs to manette to watch him jack off for two hours. Are we talking about the same stream? Oh
You didn't see it
See what I watched the stream last night. Yeah, where you where he also attempted the Docs and talks his hot shit. He's
Apparently
Got my net on the mind, baby
You did you miss that part that guy seemed fucking nuts, bro
Yeah, cuz he's a fucking he's an actual real-time retard like the guy above you
Sanity dude in fucking sanity
There's no going back like the entertainment bar level was raised so fucking high like
I'm curious what entertains you about this is fucking baby viking in over here dude, I
Are you a retard you're not listening? Oh, you're a faggot. You don't want to have a debate notice that chat
Notice that it's like J-Dog, but except J-Dog just acts like Birdo and
That dude runs off. What a faggot. God. Hey, don't say that word. Can you not say that word? They just say they say something else
Anyway, yeah, so how have you been doing? Yeah, good. That's fine. That's fine
Just for the yeah
Anyways, how have you been no you're good
Oh, I'm beautiful, man. It's great. I couldn't ask for anything more. You know, beautiful by the way.
What are you up to?
I was born Tommy James. This guy was born what he is.
Yeah, daddy that's all that's all there is to know
Yeah
What do you have
Do you have a wife?
Do you have your own house?
Look at him. I could tell you all but I have it shut up, but you're like burdo. You don't want to really hear it
So what's the point? I'm gonna start talking and you're gonna start wrapping your guns. Are you gonna shut up?
For one, why do you keep bringing up kids like having kids is some kind of like oh my god, I have kids
You don't even have kids
Bro, praise God any woman I would have had kids with it wouldn't have
Worked out very well for them. Plus imagine bringing kids into this world and being proud about it. Listen
I don't give a fuck about your family, dude. I don't
But what I will say is that's not a drop that that's not a that's that's not a plus
I get more money. You know, you know, my money goes to me. I don't have to raise any kids
I don't have a wife
It's a senior citizen and half retarded probably super annoying probably gonna have to start wiping her ass pretty soon
Or the other way around
I believe you've had fucking everyone and their brother wantin' to fucking take a swing at your punk ass.
Oh yeah, no, I can swing, I just don't want to.
I just want to stick your head in your...
I have people want to kill me.
I have people want to kill me, yeah.
You know why that is?
They can't kill me.
You know why they want to though?
You enlighten us.
No, you tell me.
I don't know.
Remember I'm Richard
All these people just want to hurt you for no reason, but you didn't do anything, right? Oh, no, I talk a lot of shit
So by the size that you're in shape of your head and the obvious brain damage like you either had a stroke
or you're like gonna act like you have dementia.
So it makes me think like you have definitely
taken some blows, dude.
You've taken some hard ones.
I'm not on their level.
Too many people like a genius, too many people like a genius.
So like.
Tommy, do you have a degree?
Do you have a degree?
Well, I have a degree.
Have I ever worked for a while?
Have you ever worked for the military?
Fuck the police!
What do you want?
Fuck the cops!
I do a hundred percent agree.
Why are you bringing it up?
Do you ever work through the cops?
I never worked for the police.
Having kids and a retard wife,
like that's some kind of flex.
How's that?
I have no retarded wife.
Definitely do.
That's why you got away with posting your pictures everywhere like you did.
Boosting pictures.
Okay, boosting pictures by the way.
Posted I said, why are you rocking like that Tom? Is that your artistic?
I like you Tommy. I like you bro regardless of I do like you. I know I have no hate I have no hate toward you man
I think you're a cool guy
Birdo thing Birdo literally wants me to like fuck it in the ass and it's like it'll never happen
It's never going to happen
Birdo two different animals mean birdo two different. I'm a dog
Two different animals from the same zoo for sure
But no, I like you Tommy. I like your rap. I guess talk shit, man
It probably works with some people but not the ones around here, but not normal people
Absolutely never going to glaze or pat you on the back, but you did take the link
and a lot of people don't.
So let's at least look at them for that.
Cause I mean, these people in the chat need a laugh.
I need a laugh.
And in order for that to happen, you gotta camera.
It makes it better.
Oh, here's this other retard.
Okay, so you want to talk all that fucking top of shit is that really you really want to sit up there fucking do
Like don't even think that you thought I wasn't fucking listening, but I was actually listening
I never said once that I wanted to fuck you
Don't put fucking words in my fucking mouth that did not as you know say so you're fucking lying
I would never
You look like a fucking Patrick version of like a fucking scum, and you look like someone that doesn't even watch their own fucking ass.
Like seriously, that's what the fuck you look like, and then you're gonna try to sit up there and act as if I want to get it, have anything sexual, do what you're not, you're fucking delusional.
That's what you don't fucking understand. Yeah, that's the thing though, no girl will ever fuck you, not even a guy will actually know fuck you, like, you know, nobody even fucking wants your ass, that's why you're exactly gonna remain, you know, fucking single like you are right now, so there's that.
So, like, shut your little, you know, fucking dumbass up.
That's the best thing you could fucking do.
You already lost the battle, I mean, earlier.
So, there, there's that.
And you thought that I wasn't actually gonna be able to actually, you know,
run out of, actually, a self-sacrifice.
Yeah, I actually had a fucking meeting today.
That's why I was like, yeah, that's why I, you know, like,
like, I'm fucking my strength.
But I didn't ask you to race me, I mean, for any of that.
I didn't race for your right strength.
No, I didn't.
I know the fuck I did.
So, there's that.
So shut your little fucking dumbass up and stop fucking lying out of your fucking ass, okay?
Because you made a fool of me out of yourself and bitch you're never gonna lay a fucking hand on me
Because that's one thing so you know for sure
I really don't fucking stomp your little duck, you know, bitch ass. I will really, you know, pick you up
and never fucking sling your fucking ground mother fucker. That's what I would do and you know do to you
Bitch, I chew people like you up for a fucking lunch
I would eat you up for breakfast, lunch, and dinner, motherfuckers.
That's what the fuck I would do.
And there'll be no fucking leftovers, I mean, neither.
So that's where I'm going to fucking find out if you really want to.
You don't get fucking snatched up with real people like you.
I mean, actually, you know, all the reality is you're really not, right?
People like, like you really get their mess.
I mean, if you actually listen up for a minute, right?
Seriously, if you actually grew up at the time, I would say.
Like, like dude, you wouldn't even be able to have any teeth, you wouldn't even be able to have any teeth at your top.
Your jaw will actually be reshaped, okay?
Along with your fucking face and the rest of you.
And that's what the fuck, you know, honestly, you know, it's a fair stat.
Right, so watch your fucking limits motherfuckers. That's what you're better
You just made a fool of me out of yourself like do you don't even got no fucking muscles
Again, you seem to
So, like I said, you already made a fool of me out of yourself, it's you.
Like, dude, you were actually no match for me, it gets me more and much better.
You made it out of me thinking that you actually are, but I already made it out of you, and I really know it.
Like, dude, I got more muscles, you know, me and my fucking bones, I made it to you.
You have nothing but actually, you know, fat. That's all the fuck you got.
But yet again, you ain't from being a fucking gangster, I mean, to wearing a fucking cowboy hat, no, let's say you're a cowboy.
Yeah, you know, let's say you're going like, yeah, yeah, no, no, let's say you're doing that, right?
No, no, let's say you want to be something completely different.
That's what the fuck you don't like, you don't get, so there's that.
And so why are you getting so fucking upset when I, when I had you know,
We call it the fucking obvious.
Yeah, you get so mad and upset when someone
acts you, you know, triggered too happy.
But you know, I'm the one to act you,
I was making the truth, but I'm like you,
you can't act you know, do that whatsoever.
That is your fucking problem, I may do.
You gotta fucking comprehend you, I'm in problem.
Like I said, we all know that you got,
you got fucking, you know, a disability.
We all fucking know it.
You don't gotta be a fucking shame of it.
This is on me the thing though. I got autism. I mean myself. I'm autistic again, but that's what Bob's at least I'm very smart
And I'm very intelligent. At least I have a fucking car at least I can fucking get around about myself
At least I was just you know, out in the fucking, you know, community, you know, helping someone out
At least I was at you know, I'll hang it out with fucking friends. I'm like, I'm like you
We were the fuck were you at you know, doing absolutely nothing. You were just sitting up there in that fucking house
If you were to watch my stream, if you were to watch my stream, you would have seen I literally came home from someone's house last night. I show the people I live with. We smoke. Yeah, they're roommates, but we're also friends. That's what makes it so great.
I got him hard. I got that dude like way too hard or something by just being me. I don't know. It's crazy. It's fucking ugly. It's disgusting. It's kind of scary.
Actually, what's up? How's it going?
Yeah
Wanted to get pounded up
That's why yeah, but uh, what else do you see you I miss you
Well, man, you know, it's unfortunate that you had to leave the way you left yesterday, you know be this panel
But I guess
You know be the like the argue, you know be the like they go in so yeah
Well, thank you for having my back there. I do feel like you had my back a little bit there and like
You were
What do you see with that?
She going at Gemnig, you know, they didn't
Do anything did she
I thought it's morning. Yeah, she was mad at Jim Nick for some reason and then she was getting really upset
Here's the thing if Jim Nick and her fallout
She's honest be hard to have relationships with anybody
They're very similar. So I don't know. I honestly think Bita might
Apologize, but maybe I'm looking too far to this guy. I don't know
Tommy now, do you think that beater should apologize or gymnast?
I think they I don't I kind of think they both should or is that like am I off on that?
They're both wasted, right? You know how it is. Tell me you ain't ever got wasted with one of your boys and
End up like throwing hands after the bar and like my
It'll be all right, you know
But we've been are different, you know what I'm saying they're very very emotional beings and they run off emotion
Sometimes so maybe it's not gonna be the same. I don't know
I do not fucking know but it's sad. It's sad to hear be that I mean
There's nothing to say this and I got a balance
It's kind of because I just came up here to put on 10 dogs into doubt. He served
Tell me tell me that ain't an easy trade-off, but anyway
Jim knit with the want to want to be on a live top that really distresses me and then be you know with the
I'm gonna die alone never gonna
Never gonna get a little chicken skin played with again
Here's the thing, Bita never gonna, feels like she,
Bita feels like she's never gonna get her little,
her little niblets nod on again.
You feel me?
And it's fucking with her, I feel like.
She's no way!
She has big cops with vlogger,
and then vlogger just counts her out.
Black out the cops in her,
and calling her an uncle effort,
or uncle fucker.
Why am I censoring myself?
oh
you know like
bloggers laughing his ass off and she did you see that and she tripped no
I'm never talking to you again blogger
It's crazy. It was crazy. It was
hopefully, hopefully,
random whatever dude that joined
the stream. He thinks what
blogger does that he thinks
blogger begging the neck to
watch him jack his little his
little red rocket off his like
like uh I don't understand
that. Tell me that I'm off
there like
Dude if that's not content, it's funny the first time not for two hours
It's a pretty creepy move and it's not just for the stream
He hits these ladies up after the stream and tries to jack his little dick off
He thinks his dick is big because he's five and a half inches
So or five feet five inches. He probably is five and a half inches back
Not like I'm sizing them up, but let's be honest. You're just a small dude
He was last night. All he was talking about is big and how he's it was bad. I'm surprised. No one saw that like
They were he was just going on to the point towards like dude. Are you brain damaged as well like
What the fuck, you're like in La La Land.
Yeah, something else dude, and I would have hopefully somebody clipped it hopefully somebody
clipped it you know that way, trip kick was around I know trip got it trip got it on that
and I you know I already know you know what he likes to clip he got us because he was
in chat and he always says if he's in chat you know he's flipping
uh but i'm just saying that like that's just sitting here in your mom's garage you know begging
some internet girl to fucking watch you play with to me that's sad the only reason i didn't join
is because i was over at a friend's house literally like in bed
I thought her and BG had something going on.
No, I think she's got a whole-ass boyfriend too,
that like she's really into,
which makes what blogger does even more sick
and like retarded and like,
trended her like once again.
If he was in jail, he's one of the guys that's done it.
He's waiting till a nurse walk by and...
I wish I was just fucking talking shit, but I know these archetypes. He's not a good guy. I've dealt with him. He's fucking already got rumor vibes with the city thing, and ooh, give me dex, dex. And yeah, they're legal overnight girls or whatever. But come on, you're like 45, and they can't even drink yet. What the fuck, dude? It's weird. It's weird.
And when I met longer actually this tells you how much work he's had done
I was 32, I think and I and I asked him about my dog
How old are you man? And he's like, oh I'm 43 or something. Oh, no. It's like I'm 39
About to be 40 and I'm like, holy shit
He's had a lot of work done. Don't let the pro talk
Look like that. I mean, it's like that's kind of weird
Yo, Arthur you saw firsthand how he is
Creepy little bastard
Watch me stroke my red rocket. I love my job. I
Like your yo real quick. I'll be honest wait for you to run up on blackout
Here. Oh, trust me. I'm not there. You guys know I can't take you much, right?
No, don't say too much man content incoming. Yeah, no, don't say too much content in coming and I just mean that
IRL getting some last back like this is all
Blackout might break his neck again. Let's just say that. Well, I
What else? Hey spunky what's going on spunky?
Chunky I subbed you so when you go live
I'm there man
I'm in it. Oh chat
I'm all over new
In there. We all up in that
I never knew blackout Andy was indian bro. What the fuck?
Yeah, you don't have anything or something like that
When I started with blackout, he was super respectful kind quiet and nice kind of the opposite of blogger
Which makes some of the pair for streaming, but I'm gonna be all up in their fucking lemonade
So it comes through it's all I'm gonna I need to find out exactly what it is
But I'm gonna see if I can get the time off
I'm just gonna make it a point. I'm gonna be there. What's up Arthur? Good how are you doing today?
How are you? You know just the dad responsibilities now, you know gotta do what I gotta do
If you can do it cool if you can't I understand but I do enjoy your little reenactment
What do I say the reenactment?
imitations of blogger and B to
if you can do some of that, that'd be pretty cool because I have to jump off here, but I'll be listening for a second, but I got something I got to go do for a little bit.
But a nice thanks for letting me come up here and cook.
Sweet P he man chunky J one everybody in chat.
I
No, no Arthur you guys what time it is that random dude though. Fuck you. You're weird. Oh
You do don't want to have a convo. You just want to run away
Later guys
Later, so that's everyone doing good to see you again our third. It's been a while sleep
Yeah, where have you guys been you guys don't like me anymore? What? I'm a whole parent now, man. You know, I can't be doing shit. Oh
Congratulations
Thank you. I didn't
Know you're expecting so congratulations. I did not know
You're having a great time. Thank you, man. Life is not the same anymore
And you think it's a good idea to announce it on the internet with a bunch of trolls
Yeah, man, I got triplets. Yes
All right, so you psyche line see you should feel some type of world
Don't let him guess anyways, I don't want to say too much there my psyche, but thank you. Okay. Okay
I enjoy you using the AI. It seems like you're you know now the perfect use for it
Because I think you're doing it a couple weeks ago now you're like
You found a perfect subtle way to use
Yeah, well I was using it, you know
We're to make some introduction videos for the show and now that I made those, you know, I
Basically just can focus on doing the music and usually the cars and stuff and I'm making a deck and stuff and so
I'm I'm enjoying my ability
Have a good time
Am I crazy or did I hear you use your old theme song a couple weeks ago?
Yeah, I can use that now. Yeah, DJ lecture actually got to the United States copyright for that song. Oh, wow
Nice, can you play it right now? It's been a while. I miss this
I'll play I'll play it later
I think she's a better friend to you than Bita everyone's just saying that's just wait. Wait. Come on man. Come on
Don't talk about Bita like that
I've been listening though, you know when I do listen
What do you think about that? What do you think about it?
Bita whenever she's here. He's always criticizing psyche. She's always like, well, but you know, you are a very bad friend
You know, you never stand up for me
But then when she goes over there, she completely shouldn't know who so yeah
Do you feel that way psyche? I mean, how do you feel about it? I mean, I feel like she I mean
She's just been like really mean and like for like no reason really. She's just like mad at everything. She's like
Call it call it the same bad things about me. I don't know but since she'll say I'm saying stuff about her
I'm trying not to but uh, you know what?
Yeah, she mentions your donations. She's like you're a total different person now to the donations
But then she's always bringing up. No, if you guys want me to do something it'll cost you $25
Come on Arthur you pushing it. No, it's the truth and whether she wants to call it
Alcohol confidence and like the alcohol speaking and it's not her
What do they usually say a drunk man's thoughts? No a drunk man's words or a sober man's thoughts
Right. Well, sometimes sometimes but you know, sometimes it's just being drunk is just like, you know, I can get dumb sometimes
You know, we all get you know, we all like it say things we regret sometimes we all get emotional
Sometimes you said the key words sometimes it seems like it's always a repetitive thing with that one
You know
Something it's always I love you. I love you. I love you. And then the next day, you know, you're a fucking scumbag
You switch for the money, you know
Yeah, flip flop that's what you're saying
What I'm saying
Well, you know, it's the truth breath
Come on, man. The chat knows the truth, too.
That's why the problem dislikes by a lot of these content creators,
because I speak the truth.
They don't call me the flip-flopper, but I just call them out.
You know, I do it without being malicious.
Well, what is the truth?
I'm not not seeing anybody, you know?
I don't care for anyone's info.
You know look as they I used to call him out a lot back then and then he would be like oh, you're an effort
You know you want to hug me?
Meanwhile, I was listening yesterday. I think and he was on panel with the training and the training was like
Saying some crazy shit to him. I'm like yo
And I'm like yo
I never said anything like that to him and this guy would like trigger even get triggered with me, but I
Guess training is different for him. I don't know well
She was also like I don't know do you this guy named auto there's a guy named auto that came came around and
Yeah, yeah that guy
He's with her now too like he's been like calling her
You know auto yeah, he's been he's been he uh, I hooked him up and uh, he says she's a beautiful smile and wants to purchase their
services and all this kind of stuff
You know crazy
What is it a panel guys that joins?
Yeah
He's like a drug. He's like a drunk Hispanic guy like in an alley
Yeah, he got like he got this shirt the other night and danced for the chat cuz blue diamond told him to
He likes being like degraded like whatever. She's like, hey, you little bitch whore and he like he likes it
She says that
He was born in Canada, but the guy has like the strongest Mexican accent
Yeah, I thought it's from Honduras, but yeah, I guess he was born in Canada
No
Oh, that's wild. Yeah, I haven't met him or if I did or you know, he didn't stand out or anything
He's annoying as shit
Damn, worse than Birdo or?
Uh, right about there, bro. The guy always drinks, the guy always wants to fight with people
You know
Yeah, but he likes 40 diamonds, he likes 40 diamonds a lot
Well, I wonder why
40 diamonds making the rounds around YouTube, huh?
Not really. I mean
A lot of these people that are into trainings
He's been training
for a while
She's only been over here in Zayas
I mean where else has she been?
We'll beat us and Kate's and Samans and Samans
Yeah, like you know
Show too, but she's like taking some showers. She's actually in Minnesota right now. He's in Minnesota like working in Minnesota right now
Like you know trick it trick tricking out there in Minnesota
Is that to be closer to raging or you don't know
I'm not sure, but yeah, they are they are like pretty close and
He says they're in love
Yeah, wow
So she's she goes by flirty demon now what?
Yeah, she was my flirty demon
But uh and then uh
that uh auto calls are crazy demon and then
I don't know
Her name is wow. Her name is change
Where's the chat big hey spunky? I am ready in the chat. How are we doing?
I'm just sitting here with the Elzo and Arthur. It's been a while since I've talked to these dudes. I'm so excited
to be able to chat again
Yeah, I'm good
Yeah, I haven't you know, I've just been doing my show as usual and you know, it's been pretty crazy
ghost
Go send some big donations last week. It was pretty exciting
These are good random who don't want donate his goals don't name in that money, right?
Well, yeah, random guys donated a couple hundred bucks and and then ghost is a ghost donated a lot last week
To kind of like get some panel cloud and stuff like that and sponsor some shows and you know
He's he definitely was super generous. I'll be able to probably get a computer now and
I'm excited about that
Then I'll be able to improve my show a lot. I'll have my professional microphone hooked up. I'll have
maybe get a sound board hooked up and stuff like that and
Have a special effects that are sound effects on a board and stuff like that. That'd be cool, huh guys?
That would be Howard Stern Esk.
That's awesome.
Yeah, so we're getting there.
I'll have a professional setup, maybe some new headphones
and stuff, and professional studio headphones,
like I've always wanted to have.
Yeah, I have a great mic.
I have a professional mic.
I just haven't been able to hook it up
because I don't have my computer.
So once I get to the computer,
I'll be able to hook up a mic, so.
Oh, okay. What brand is it? Do you know? Do you remember?
It's just a it's like a professional studio microphone. I got an Amazon. It's not like it. It's not like a
It's in my closet. I can't I can go look at it a little bit, but
Um, I'll bring it out. So it's really nice. I just don't want to bring it out until I like I can plug it in because
I've been wanting to
Wanting to use it for a while. I've had it for a couple years probably
Oh
I think it was at least a hundred bucks. So it's a pretty good one
Gotta get a move on up, you know gotta move on up
Yep, I'm trying. I'm trying. Yeah, it's been as the show's going really well and
Got good guests and we haven't many Manson hasn't been back for a while
but we had a but we had a power lifter all the other day special guest power lifter if you guys
turn it into that way, his name is Daddy Bigness, and I'm going around YouTube looking for like talent
and like, you know, wanting people to like promote here, you know, I also, Spunky, I started a show,
it's like, she's that, hey, there's Spunky, you know, make sure you go see one of her lives coming up.
DJ Electra, of course, check out DJ Electra.
I think a pair of Beats are pretty good.
They've got a good microphone.
Yeah, I might get a pair of Beats.
I'll let you think it on sale.
Like maybe by this November, they'll be on sale again.
What do you think, Beats?
I think Beats would be a good one to get.
So who are we gonna hear?
Yeah
With the microphone on them, there's those ones with my microphone on them too, right?
I want I want to get those ones
I think sweet pieces they have microphones. They got microphones. Yeah, sweet pieces. They have ones with microphone
Oh, okay. I didn't know that maybe I'll look into those. I think they'd probably be good for broadcasting
So
Alice may or if she donated one time. Oh
Yeah, she's yes, he's been here a couple times. I interviewed her a couple times. She's really cool. I like her a lot and
She's gorgeous as well. And you know also has very interesting stories and a back interesting background
So I really enjoy having her on the show
She talked about her porn star life and all that
Yeah, she did she did
she told a lot of interesting stories and you know about all kinds of stuff and
like you know we did a couple hour long at least hour long one-on-ones it was
pretty interesting so I like her a lot and so hopefully she comes back on a lot
of shimmers use them sweepies as the way for the Prime Day sale yeah they just
had a Prime Day too I just like you know I didn't get too much stuff on the Prime
Day sale this year but next year
Or maybe I'll have another one this year. Hopefully, you know, yeah, they have a couple
Yeah, they just had one not that long ago, but they they have these we had a couple here like two three
Look good, I'm just trying to get
That's why I got access to my chat on this tablet and so I'm trying to get in the chat right now
How's everyone doing
Yeah
It's good that the old crews back together the old man
Yeah, would you go bring it to us three?
Yeah, it's like, yeah
You've had a lot of new people around like earlier you had um
the girl who's talking about her daughter, you know, her situation, and then fucking
school of Athens, bro, the guy's a scumbag.
She's crying about her daughter passing away, do you believe in God?
It's like what?
Yeah, well, yeah, he's a little bit forceful, but yeah, he's a good guy
He donated today like you know five bucks and so I'll give him a little bit of a leeway
Yeah, you know money over everything
Like went over to like MSI
Or other people, you know, and it's not really side that I like I don't I don't want those people to take sides
I never asked people to take sides about for anybody like, you know, it's like watch whoever you want to watch
But some people like what people to take sides of me and like, you know
What you and Zaya
No
Yeah, a little bit bad, but yeah, I'm pretty sure it's been back on the show and she's been in chat once a while
Yes, she's doing good
We've made up
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Yeah, I feel like it's calling in or you know video in like I don't know how you would you know say it like
Because we're getting time you see the little time on stream stream yard has a little time on it
Yeah, it's only so it's you know you're getting time. It's a call
It is it's a call we see yeah, so yeah cause we people don't know about that how it's during life, you know
Yeah
So call back in
And I finished my coffee
Well, you want to take talk Arthur or no, I guess now you don't have time for it now
Yeah, it's a little I started doing a like a little sour show on it
No, I do go I've been going every day I still got my every day and I still go but I um, you know, sometimes I
I, uh, you know, just feel like doing readings and it's like on TikTok is just fast-paced readings and stuff like that
and then uh, I kind of can get
Also advertising for my private readings there and also I can advertise for the youtube show
So I think I may have some
TikTok people coming over here saying hi and like, you know adding more people to the chat
I do like that's how I got a lot of people in the chat the first place was like networking and so
Yeah, so definitely that's like probably the best way to uh
To build as soon as you end it over there you start up over here. I assume
Well, yeah, but I'll do it like maybe before go to bed
But if I feel like just doing a fast-paced show like you know in the middle of the night or something like that
I can just do a tick-tock. It's like it's pretty pretty fast energy and it's like, you know, just it's different than YouTube
It's completely different platform. So it's a different out of audience to and I guess I get to do more of the readings
Which I like to do and so
So it's been going pretty well
I think it'd be a better idea if you go live there an hour right before you start up here
and you get a bunch of new people there and you tell them, yo, you know, follow the new, follow the YouTube channel
Yeah, I do that. I do that sometimes. I do that sometimes. I do, I do, I've done both. I've done, yeah, I've done both. I've done that, and it works good. I'll continue to do it and stuff, so
Yeah, it's just
I'm already I'm already monetized there, too. I'm already monetized on tiktok like within three days
I was basically ready to monetize there. So
And my I have over a hundred memberships now in this in this channel over a hundred memberships
Memberships yeah memberships
No wonder be this jealous this fix
It is uh, it's going pretty well more sense. Imagine that what's the cheapest on your membership?
This is it's a dollar 499 that's like, you know, yeah five dollars times a hundred
That's five hundred a month. Yeah, but it is like, you know, you two just take a percentage of it
Yeah, maybe maybe maybe maybe like 300 you know out of the 500
I think it's like 250 just to be sick. Okay. Yeah
be this person because of that.
That makes a lot more sense now.
Well, she could monetize her show.
I mean, it's like, I think she'll probably do.
Exactly, we can too, but she doesn't want to
because now it's like people are gonna say,
oh, you're copying what he does,
but she doesn't want to admit that she wants what she does.
Everyone copies everyone. It's like people like get ideas from places and I adapt. Yeah, I get inspired
I adapt I adapt ideas like the clapping system. I've seen on other shows like you know and like and also the
You know and also like not starting the sponsoring panels. I've seen before, you know, so it's like I just like
You know, it's not maybe I could work when it we're working into my format, especially because there's like a lot of people that like ours haters
And stuff like that. And so maybe I can even monetize the hate on the show. And so that's
so I did and
I know I think people can take my ideas too. I mean, it's like we can all share and like there's like a lot of
Lot of people out there. There's a lot of shows. There's like a you know, there's plenty of
audience
Billions of people in the world like a lot of people are looking for this
I mean they haven't found it yet
so we have to find the people and like bring them in to the panel burst and like
Keep growing it and like we'll have a lot more interesting characters
We'll have like the new character unlocked. I'll be like every day like every hour will have like
Interesting new characters coming on and stuff like that because there's all these interesting people around the world just looking for us
Yeah
So what do you think guys we're gonna we're gonna maybe like take this to another level like every cool
Because I want everyone to be making money and everyone to be you know
it's like able to monetize and and
Have fun and it makes the money too
It's like not just about having fun for me because it's like I want to do this as a you know
Main main career and like you know a lot of my time and put a lot of my time energy
Like a love into this and it's going pretty well. So it's worthwhile. You know, like I had a what's his name?
Chris K was like saying, oh
Nobody makes money on YouTube. We don't just ever watch you quit YouTube. It's just a waste of time
I'm like, well, I'm making money on YouTube. It's like so I mean, it's it is possible
It's like he's on rumble and stuff like that and rumble doesn't have the potential of like YouTube. It's like
YouTube is like
Chris K gets like two viewers
Well, yeah, but it's like, you know, it's like there's ways to like increase viewership
But it's like you can't just like go out harass homeless people and call it a stream and say of course you're gonna get yeah
Yeah, I mean, it's like that's why you got kicked off a YouTube
I guess because well, I don't know but he didn't pass very long on YouTube
I don't know how I've lasted but it's like, you know
Somehow like the angels have been with me and like, you know protecting me like on this platform somehow
I'm still here
Yeah, the good electrified
Yeah, you know, like I love a lecture. You compare her to B. That's a big difference
Remember what I was saying, you know, it's like a lecture like, you know
Help me out of that copyright issue and everything and she's like help me with like the everything and that you know and really
Like without her I don't know if my show would be here because I was getting that I was getting the claims rejected and stuff like that
You know and then because I wasn't writing the letter in the right way, but then she showed me how to
what to write on the letter, and basically it turned things around for me. I was able to get all the stuff removed.
There was just like she was she was really the huge part of me keeping my channel
But also beta and page also like they did like a you know like a good lob attraction like a
Positive thinking kind of spell with me and that that helped a lot too
And so I appreciate everybody that helped me in that but I'll say like a lecture actually like you know
Like she missed her like nephew's hockey game and like did others other stuff
So she could like help me like a few of those nights and a critical time
and she really did help the channel and you know and so that's why I gave her so special like you
know kudos that day but I didn't mean to like say that you know anybody anybody else was any
less or anything like that but she had she really did help me more than anybody like and especially
when I felt like I hadn't like nobody could help me she was actually able to so um so thank you
Hopefully everyone's doing good today
Yeah, so
I'm just chilling today. I finished my coffee. I'll say for a little longer. Anyone want to hop up on panel?
I got the link pinned
Hopefully a chat's having a good day. Hey chance chicken army. You got some members other shout out sweet pea chance chicken army
I want to shout out
All the members that I see the chat. Let's see
Maz Nick Johnson
He man is a member and a mod
We got hey, there's spunky a mod
And
We got you know, it's just like a lot of great friends here
nobody's a mod and
And guys so you can go to hey there spunky and spunky has the sergeant of show. I really want to support her new show I
Want to make sure I see it. Hopefully I will cash it next time and
If I do if I do happen to be streaming and like she's on let me know and I'll end my stream and I'll
Go ahead and send everyone over there
Because I really want to help people out also, you know page
page is also doing a show too as
very
Prairie winds and wildflower spiritual arts
You can go say hi to Paige on her show if she's I think hopefully she's enjoying doing her show. I heard I
Know she's doing really well. I've seen a few of her shows and she's awesome, you know
So go check out page
Anybody want to hop up
Let me see it is 12 I've been on for three and a half hours. I might just take a little
Afternoon nap, but there are 40 people here
So if there are is anybody that wants to talk about anything or and I am I did finish the coffee. So, you know, I
Have a little bit energy left. I'll finish this one. I'll finish this one coffee. Oh
Okay
I'm sorry
Okay guys well I
Think I'm gonna be back a little bit
I'll be back tonight guys. Okay
No, no, no, I'm gonna take off for a little while and take a little nap and stuff, but I'll be back
Okay, I love you guys. I'll be back later. Okay
Love you spunky. I'll see you guys soon
Are you gonna come back with a drink?
I have another coffee left. I might I'll see if I buy guys love you. I'll see I'll see how I feel like an hour
I'll see you soon guys. I love you. Okay. Wow